<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>A Collection of choice books in divinity, history, philosophy,   herauldry, horsemanship, husbandry with variety of books of voyages, travels, as also of romances, plays, novels &amp;c. curiously bound, will  be exposed to sale by way of auction at Bridges Coffee-House in Popes-Head-Alley over against the Royal Exchange in Cornhill on Monday the 8th day ofFebruary 1685/6 / by Edward Millington ...</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <editionStmt>
            <edition>
               <date>1686</date>
            </edition>
         </editionStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 154 KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 19 1-bit group-IV TIFF page images.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2014-11">2014-11 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">A69774</idno>
            <idno type="STC">Wing C5119</idno>
            <idno type="STC">ESTC R29638</idno>
            <idno type="EEBO-CITATION">11184697</idno>
            <idno type="OCLC">ocm 11184697</idno>
            <idno type="VID">46599</idno>
            <availability>
               <p>To the extent possible under law, the Text Creation Partnership has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights to this keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above, according to the terms of the CC0 1.0 Public Domain Dedication (http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/). This waiver does not extend to any page images or other supplementary files associated with this work, which may be protected by copyright or other license restrictions. Please go to https://www.textcreationpartnership.org/ for more information about the project.</p>
            </availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online text creation partnership.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. A69774)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 46599)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Early English books, 1641-1700 ; 1438:12 or 1710:20)</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>A Collection of choice books in divinity, history, philosophy,   herauldry, horsemanship, husbandry with variety of books of voyages, travels, as also of romances, plays, novels &amp;c. curiously bound, will  be exposed to sale by way of auction at Bridges Coffee-House in Popes-Head-Alley over against the Royal Exchange in Cornhill on Monday the 8th day ofFebruary 1685/6 / by Edward Millington ...</title>
                  <author>Chiswell, Richard.</author>
                  <author>Millington, Edward, d. 1703.</author>
               </titleStmt>
               <extent>[4], 28 [i.e. 32] p.   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>s.n.],</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
                  <date>1685/6.</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>Attributed to Richard Chiswell by Wing.</note>
                  <note>This item appears at reel 1438:12 as Wing C5119, and at reel 1710:20 as Wing C3908.</note>
                  <note>Wing number C3908 cancelled in Wing (2nd ed.).</note>
                  <note>Irregularities in paging: last page of copy at reel 1438:12 numbered 28, copy at reel 1710:20 numbered 16, with numerous other errors; page order and contents is same in both copies.</note>
                  <note>Reproduction of originals in the Bodleian Library and the British Library.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,368 texts created during Phase 1 of the project (2000-2009), initially available only to institutions that contributed to their creation, were released into the public domain on 1 January 2015. The approximately 40,000 texts produced during Phase 2 (2009- ), of which 34,963 had been released as of 2020, originally similarly restricted, were similarly freed from all restrictions on 1 August 2020. As of that date anyone is free to take and use these texts for any purpose (modify them, annotate them, distribute them, etc.). But we do respectfully request that due credit and attribution be given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Keying and markup guidelines are available at the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp"
                       matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)"
                       replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char"
                       matchPattern="(.+)"
                       replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term>Catalogs, Booksellers' --  England.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2013-05</date>
            <label>TCP</label>Assigned for keying and markup</change>
         <change>
            <date>2013-08</date>
            <label>SPi Global</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images</change>
         <change>
            <date>2013-11</date>
            <label>Anne Simpson</label>Sampled and proofread</change>
         <change>
            <date>2013-11</date>
            <label>Anne Simpson</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited</change>
         <change>
            <date>2014-03</date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion</change>
      </revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <front>
         <div type="title_page">
            <pb facs="tcp:46599:1"/>
            <p>A COLLECTION OF Choice BOOKS, IN Divinity, Hiſtory, Philoſophy, Herauldry, Horſeman<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhip, Husbandry, with variety of Books of Voyages, Travels, as alſo of Romances, Plays, Novels, <hi>&amp;c. <hi>Curiouſly Bound.</hi>
               </hi>
            </p>
            <p>Will be expoſed to Sale by way of Auction at <hi>Bridges</hi> Coffee-Houſe in <hi>Popes-Head-Alley</hi> over-againſt the <hi>Royal Exchange</hi> in <hi>Cornhill,</hi> on <hi>Monday</hi> the 8th day of <hi>February,</hi> 1685/6.</p>
            <p>By <hi>Edward Millington,</hi> Bookſeller.</p>
            <p>Catalogues are diſtributed from Mr. <hi>Notts</hi> at the <hi>Queens Arms</hi> in <hi>Pell-Mell,</hi> Mr. <hi>Wilkinſons</hi> at the <hi>Black Boy</hi> in <hi>Fleet-ſtreet,</hi> Mr. <hi>Miller</hi> at the <hi>Acorn</hi> in St. <hi>Pauls Church-Yard,</hi> and at the above-mentioned <hi>Bridges</hi> Coffee-Houſe, 1685/6.</p>
         </div>
         <div type="to_the_reader">
            <pb facs="tcp:46599:2"/>
            <pb facs="tcp:46599:2"/>
            <head>To the READER.</head>
            <p>THIS <hi>Catalogue</hi> conſiſts of ſo many Excellent Books of the beſt Authors, that have treated of the Subjects mentioned in the Title Page, that I will not queſtion the Judgment of the Gentlemen the Buyers, by giving a particular Recommendatory Character of them. The Hiſtorical Part, both Forreign and Domestick, is the beſt and compleateſt that hath hitherto been preſented to the World; and if the names of many Authors and their Hiſtories, not hither<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>to to knowable, hath been acceptable, and confeſſedly uſeful to ſe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>veral Gentlemen, I may much more reaſonably promiſe to my ſelf the expoſing the Books this way to Sale, will be extreamly deſirable, eſpecially if they will he pleaſed to conſider, that not one half of them mentioned in the enſuing <hi>Catalogue</hi> are by reaſon of their ſcarcity, at all times to be found, or at any Rate procured, when really wanted. I might further intimate. That ſome of the valuable Books are of the great Paper, and moſt of them as to their Binding, ſufficiently inviting, anſwering the preſent Mode, and commendable modern Faſhion of moſt Bookiſh Gentlemens Libraries, being generally curiouſly and richly bound.</p>
            <p>This Sale will begin on <hi>Monday</hi> the Eighth day of <hi>February, 1685/6,</hi> at <hi>Bridges Coffee Houſe,</hi> in <hi>Popes Head Alley,</hi> in <hi>Corn<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hil,</hi> from the Hours of <hi>9</hi> to <hi>12</hi> in the Morning, and from <hi>2</hi> in the Afternoon till <hi>7</hi> in the Evening, continuing daily till all the Books are ſold.</p>
         </div>
         <div type="note">
            <pb facs="tcp:46599:3"/>
            <head>Conditions of Sale.</head>
            <p n="1">I. THat he who bids moſt, is the Buyer, and if any Difference ariſe which the Company cannot decide, then the Book or Books ſhall forthwith be Expoſed to Sale again.</p>
            <p n="2">II. That all the Books in this Catalogue, not otherwiſe ex<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>preſſed, (for ought we know) are perfect; but if any of them appear to be otherwiſe before they be taken away, the Buyer ſhall have his Choice of taking or leaving them.</p>
            <p n="3">III. That the Money for the Book or Books ſo bought, is to be paid at the Place of Sale within a Fortnight after the Auction is ended; where the Book or Books ſo bought, ſhall be ready to be delivered.</p>
            <p n="4">IV. That the Books will be expoſed to view from 9 to 12 in the Morning, and from 2 to 6 in the Evening, for one whole Week preceding the Sale, to all Gentlemen, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> which by the Undertaker is deſired, the Books being extraordinarily qualified as to the binding, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
            </p>
         </div>
      </front>
      <body>
         <div type="list">
            <pb n="1" facs="tcp:46599:3"/>
            <head>
               <hi>Divinity</hi> in Folio.</head>
            <list>
               <item>1 BIſhop <hi>Andrews</hi> XCVI Sermons, with a Sermon at his Funeral, <hi>Lond.</hi> 1629</item>
               <item>2 St. <hi>Amour</hi>'s Journal of the 5 Propoſitions between Janſeniſts and Moliniſts 1661</item>
               <item>3 <hi>Ainſworth</hi>'s <hi>(H.)</hi> Annotations on the Pentateuch, Pſalms, and Canticles 1639</item>
               <item>4 St. <hi>Auguſtine</hi> of the City of God, with the Comment of <hi>Jo. Lodov. Vives</hi> 1620</item>
               <item>5 <hi>Alleſtree's</hi> (Dr. <hi>Rich.</hi>) 18 Sermons before the King, (large Paper) a little imperfect 1669</item>
               <item>6 Bible with Common-Prayer, <hi>Apocrypha</hi> and Pſalms, large Roman Letter <hi>Ox.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>7 Book of Common-Prayer, (with the late Alterations for the King, <hi>&amp;c. Ox.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>8 Book of Homilies, appointed to be read in Churches by Queen <hi>Elizabeth Lond.</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>9 Bp <hi>Brownrigg</hi>'s Sermons (compleat, in one Volume) <hi>Lond.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>10 <hi>Baxter</hi>'s <hi>(R.)</hi> Chriſtian Directory; or Body of Practical Divinity 1678</item>
               <item>11 —Catholick Theology, for pacification of the Dogmatical word, Warriours 1675</item>
               <item>12 <hi>Burnets (Gilb.)</hi> Hiſtory of the Reformation of the Church of <hi>England.</hi> 2 Vol. 1679, 81</item>
               <item>13 <hi>Ball</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Power of Godlineſs; with five diſtinct Treatiſes <hi>Lond.</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>14 <hi>Brooks</hi> (Dr. <hi>Matth.</hi>) myſterious Hiſtory of Man's Redemption 1657</item>
               <item>15 <hi>Charnock</hi>'s <hi>(Steph.)</hi> Works, <hi>viz.</hi> of Divine Providence, on the Attributes, With all his other Diſcourſes, in two Vol. 1684</item>
               <item>16 <hi>Cave</hi> (Dr. <hi>William</hi>) Lives of the Apoſtles and Primitive Fathers, (large Paper) compleat, in 2 Volumes 1677</item>
               <item>17 <hi>Combers</hi> (Dr. <hi>Tho.</hi>) his Works, <hi>viz.</hi> A Companion to the Temple, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>18 <hi>Chillingworth</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Religion of Proteſtants, a ſafe way to Salvation (beſt Edit.) 1684</item>
               <item>19 <hi>Cradock</hi>'s <hi>(S.)</hi> Hiſtory of the Old Teſtament, methodiz'd; with a Hiſtory of Jewiſh Affairs 1683</item>
               <item>20 <hi>Cauſin (F. N.)</hi> of the Command of Reaſon over the Paſſions 1638</item>
               <item>21 <hi>Downam</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Chriſtian Warfare, againſt the Devil, World, and Fleſh 1634</item>
               <item>22 <hi>Durham</hi>'s <hi>(Ja.)</hi> Commentary upon the Book of the <hi>Revelation Lond.</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>23 <hi>Frank</hi> (Dr. <hi>Mark</hi>) his Courſe of Sermons, with a Sermon at S. <hi>Pauls</hi> Croſs <hi>Lond.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>24 <hi>Goodwin</hi> (Dr. <hi>Tho.</hi>) Expoſition on the <hi>Revelation,</hi> Diſcourſe of the Knowledg of God, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>25 <hi>Gell</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Rob.</hi>) Remains. Pious Notes and Obſervations on the New Teſtament 1676</item>
               <item>26 <hi>Gurnall</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Chriſtian in compleat Armour: Or Saints War againſt the Devil 1679</item>
               <item>27 <hi>Hooker</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Of the Laws of Eccleſiaſtical Polity, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> (beſt Edition, with the Author's Life 1682</item>
               <item>28 <hi>Horton</hi> (Dr. <hi>Tho.</hi>) his 100 Sermons on ſeveral Texts of the Old and New Teſt. 1679</item>
               <item>29 <hi>Hutcheſon (Geo.)</hi> his Expoſition of St. <hi>John</hi>'s Goſpel <hi>Lond.</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>30 Harmony, Chronicle and Order of the New Teſtament, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> By <hi>J. Lightfoot</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>31 <hi>Hammond</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Hen.</hi>) Practical Diſcourſes, <hi>viz.</hi> Practical Catech. <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>32 —Polemical Tracts, <hi>viz.</hi> Diſcourſes in defence of the Ch. of <hi>Eng.</hi> in point of Schiſm, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>33 <hi>Heylin (Peter)</hi> Sum of Chriſtian Theology, or Expoſition of the Creed 1673</item>
               <item>34 <hi>Hacket</hi>'s (Bp) Century of Sermons, on ſeveral remarkable Subjects 1675</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:46599:4"/>
               <item>35 Jeſuits Morals, faithfully extracted out of the Jeſuits own Books <hi>Lond.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>36 <hi>Jenkins (Will.)</hi> Expoſition of the Epiſtle of <hi>Jude</hi> (compleat, in one Vol.) 1656</item>
               <item>37 <hi>Keach (B.)</hi> his Key to open Scripture-Metaphors, (both Parts, in one Vol.) 1682</item>
               <item>38 Key of the Bible, with the Metrical Verſion of the Pſalms. By Dr. <hi>Fr, Roberts</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>39 King <hi>James</hi> his Tranſlation of <hi>David</hi>'s Pſalms <hi>Lond.</hi> 1636</item>
               <item>40 <hi>Lightfoot</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>John</hi>) Works, <hi>viz.</hi> Chron. &amp; Harm. of Old and N. Teſt. <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 2 vol. 1684</item>
               <item>41 <hi>Littleton</hi> (Dr. <hi>Adam</hi>) his 61 Sermons, (moſt upon publick Occaſions) 1680</item>
               <item>42 <hi>Leigh</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Annotations upon all the New Teſt. Philological and Theological 1650</item>
               <item>43 —Annotations on the five Poetical Books of the Old Teſtament 1657</item>
               <item>44 <hi>More</hi> (Dr. <hi>Hen.</hi>) his modeſt Enquiry into the Myſtery of Iniquity 1664</item>
               <item>45 <hi>Mayers</hi> (Dr. <hi>John</hi>) his Commentary upon the Old &amp; New Teſtament, in 5 Vol. <hi>Lond.</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>46 <hi>Nicholſon</hi>'s (Bp) Analyſis of the Pſalms, with a Prayer at the end of every Pſalm 1662.</item>
               <item>47 <hi>Pool</hi>'s <hi>(Mat.)</hi> Pious and Learned Annotations on the Old and New Teſt. in 2 vol. 1683</item>
               <item>48 <hi>Pearſon</hi>'s (Bp <hi>John</hi>) Expoſition of the Creed, (5th and laſt Edition) 1683</item>
               <item>49 Plea for Chriſtianity, againſt the Scepticks of this Age. By <hi>John Smith</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>50 <hi>Pemble (Will.)</hi> his Learned Works, both Theological and Philological 1635</item>
               <item>51 <hi>Robert</hi>'s <hi>(Fr.)</hi> Key of the Bible, unlocking the richeſt Treaſury of Holy Scripture 1675</item>
               <item>52 <hi>Reynolds</hi> (Bp <hi>Edw.</hi>) his Works compleat, (laſt Edition) 1679</item>
               <item>53 <hi>Sanderſon</hi>'s (Bp <hi>Rob.</hi>) XXXV Sermons (with the Life of the Author) 1681</item>
               <item>54 <hi>Stillingfleet</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Edw.</hi>) Rational Account of the Grounds of the Proteſtant Religion 1681</item>
               <item>55 <hi>Smith (John)</hi> Chriſtian Religions Appeal, to the Bar of Common Reaſon 1679.</item>
               <item>56 <hi>Shute (Joſias)</hi> his 19 Sermons on <hi>Sarah</hi> and <hi>Hagar,</hi> 16th Chap. of <hi>Geneſis</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>57 <hi>Stillingfleet</hi>'s (Dr.) Sermons, and his Diſcourſe againſt <hi>Crellius,</hi> about Chriſt's Sufferings 1681</item>
               <item>58 <hi>Taylor</hi>'s (Bp <hi>Jer.</hi>) Polemical and Moral Diſcourſes, <hi>viz.</hi> liberty of Propheſying, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>59 <hi>Towerſon's (Gabr.)</hi> Explication on the Apoſtles Creed; with an Introduction, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>60 —Explication of the Decalogue, or Ten Commandments 1685</item>
               <item>61 View of the Soul, in ſeveral Tracts. By a Perſon of Quality <hi>Lond.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>62 <hi>Wilſon</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Compleat Chriſtian Dictionary (beſt Edition, with Additions) 1678</item>
               <item>63 <hi>Willet</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Andr.</hi>) General view of Papiſtry, (with the Author's Life) 1634</item>
               <item>64 <hi>White</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>John</hi>) Works: with a defence of the way to the true Church. By <hi>F. White</hi> 1624</item>
               <item>65 Bible, with Common-Prayer, Apocripha, and Pſalms, (large Roman Letter) <hi>Ox.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>66 Bp <hi>Browning</hi>'s Sermons, (compleat, in one vol.) laſt Edition, 1685</item>
               <item>67 A Kep to open Scripture Metaphors. By <hi>Th. Delaune,</hi> and <hi>B. K.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>68 <hi>Alleſtry</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Richard</hi>) 40 Sermons before the King, and on ſolemn Occaſions 1684</item>
               <item>69 <hi>Towerſon (Gab.)</hi> Explication of the Apoſtles Creed <hi>Lond.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>70 —Explication of the Decalogue, or Ten Commandments 1681</item>
               <item>71 Common-Prayer (with the late Alteration for the King and Royal Family) <hi>Oxon.</hi>
               </item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="list">
            <head>Divinity in Quarto.</head>
            <list>
               <item>72 APocrypha, in a large Roman Letter <hi>Cambridg.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>73 —Another of the ſame, with the ſinging Pſalms</item>
               <item>74 Ancient Church-Government; a brief Account thereof, (beſt Edition) 1685</item>
               <item>75 <hi>Arrowſmith</hi> (Dr. <hi>John) Armilla Catechetica,</hi> or Chain of Principles <hi>Camb.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>76 <hi>Abbot</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Rob.</hi>) againſt Dr. <hi>Biſhop</hi>'s 2d part of the Reformation of a Catholick 1609</item>
               <pb n="2" facs="tcp:46599:4"/>
               <item>77 <hi>Atterſoll (Will.)</hi> on the Sacraments, Baptiſm, and Lord's Supper (wants Title) <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>78 <hi>Baxter</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Treatiſe of Epiſcopacy; againſt <hi>H. Dodwell</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>79 —Naked Popery, in anſwer to the Catholick Naked Truth 1677</item>
               <item>80 —Apology for the Nonconformiſts Miniſtry; with a Poſtſcript, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>81 —Second true Defence of the Meer Nonconformiſts, againſt Dr. <hi>Stillingfleet</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>82 —Life of Faith, in three parts; with a Catalogue of the Author's Works 1670</item>
               <item>83 <hi>Bridge (Will.)</hi> his Works, <hi>viz.</hi> Excellent Sermons, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> in 2 vol. 1656, 7</item>
               <item>84 <hi>Burgeſs (Anth.)</hi> Spiritual Refinings, 2d part: or, a Treatiſe of Sin, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1654</item>
               <item>85 <hi>Bunting (H.)</hi> Travels of the Holy Patriarcks, Prophets, Judges, Kings, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>86 Bible, with Common-Prayer, Apocrypha, and Singing Pſalms <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>87 Book of Common-Prayer, and Adminiſtration of the Sacraments, <hi>&amp;c. Lond.</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>88 <hi>Burrough's (Jer.)</hi> Rare Jewel of Chriſtian Contentment <hi>Lond.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>89 —Goſpel-Converſation, and Miſery of thoſe that have their Portion in this Life, 1656</item>
               <item>90 —Two Treatiſes. 1. Of Earthly-mindedneſs. 2. Heavenly Converſation, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>91 —Expoſition upon the 8, 9, and 10th Chap. of <hi>Hoſea,</hi> in ſeveral Lectures 1650</item>
               <item>92 <hi>Bentham (John)</hi> Society of Saints, delivered in 14 Sermons 1636</item>
               <item>93 <hi>Bruce (Rob.)</hi> 16 Sermons at <hi>Edinburgh,</hi> on the Lord's Supper, <hi>&amp;c. Lond.</hi> 1617</item>
               <item>94 <hi>Broughton</hi>'s <hi>(Hugh)</hi> Conſent of Holy Scriptures <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>95 <hi>Boys</hi> (Dr. <hi>John</hi>) his Remains; being Sermons on ſome proper Leſſons in the Liturgy, 1631</item>
               <item>96 <hi>Coſin</hi>'s (Bp) Scholaſtical Hiſtory of the Canon of the Holy Scripture 1672</item>
               <item>97 <hi>Clement</hi>'s Epiſtle to the <hi>Corinthians,</hi> with learned Annotations thereupon 1647</item>
               <item>98 <hi>Caryll</hi>'s Expoſition on <hi>Job,</hi> (beginning at the 11th Chap. ending the 29th) in 5 vol. <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>99 <hi>Collins</hi> (Dr. <hi>J.</hi>) his Intercourſes of Divine Love betwixt Chriſt and the Church 1676</item>
               <item>100 <hi>Donne</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>John</hi>) <gap reason="foreign">
                     <desc>〈 in non-Latin alphabet 〉</desc>
                  </gap>; or declarat. of Self-homicide, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1648</item>
               <item>101 <hi>Dod</hi> and <hi>Clever</hi>'s plain Expoſition of the Ten Commandments, 19th Edition 1662</item>
               <item>102 —Ten Sermons fitting Men for the worthy receiving the Lord's Supper 1632</item>
               <item>103 <hi>Elton (Edw.)</hi> his Expoſition on the Ten Commandments, and Lord's Prayer 1647</item>
               <item>104 <hi>Eaton</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Hony-Comb of Free-Juſtification by Chriſt alone 1642</item>
               <item>105 <hi>Falkner</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Will.</hi>) Treatiſe of Reproaching and Cenſure; with ſeveral Sermons 1689</item>
               <item>106 <hi>Flavel (John)</hi> Fountain of Life opened; or, a Diſplay of Chriſt, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>107 —His Treatiſe of the Soul of Man: of the Divine Original and Immort. Nat. 1685</item>
               <item>108 —Method of Grace, in bringing home the Eternal Redemption 1681</item>
               <item>109 —Husbandry ſpiritualiz'd: or, Heavenly Uſe of Earthly Things 1684</item>
               <item>110 Lord <hi>Falkland</hi>'s Diſcourſe of Infallibility, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> with <hi>Mountague</hi>'s Letter about changing Religion 1651</item>
               <item>111 <hi>Forbe</hi>'s <hi>(Pat.)</hi> his Learned Commentary upon the Revelation; with a Treatiſe in defence of the lawful calling of the Miniſters of the Reformed Churches, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1614</item>
               <item>112 <hi>Glanvill</hi>'s <hi>(Joſ.)</hi> Diſcourſes, Sermons, and Remains; publiſhed by Dr. <hi>Horneck</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>113 <hi>Gregory</hi>'s <hi>(J.)</hi> Notes and Obſervations upon ſome paſſages of Scripture 1650</item>
               <item>114 <hi>Greenham</hi>'s <hi>(Richard)</hi> Godly Inſtructions and Directions for all Men, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1600</item>
               <item>115 <hi>Hale</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Golden Remains, with additions of Sermons and Miſcellanies, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>116 Hiſtory of the Euchariſt. By <hi>Monſieur l' Arro<expan>
                        <am>
                           <g ref="char:abque"/>
                        </am>
                        <ex>que</ex>
                     </expan>
                  </hi> Engliſhed by <hi>J. Walker</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>117 <hi>Hall</hi> (Bp <hi>Joſ.</hi>) Of Epiſcopacy by Divine Right, aſſerted <hi>Lond.</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>118 <hi>Hugh</hi>'s (Mr.) Man of Sin: or, a Diſcourſe of Popery <hi>Lond.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>119 <hi>Huntley</hi>'s <hi>(W.)</hi> Breviate of the Prelats intollerable Uſurpations, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1637</item>
               <item>120 <hi>Hill (John)</hi> his Expoſition on the Ten Commandments, and Lord's Prayer 1625</item>
               <item>121 <hi>Jackson</hi> (Dr. <hi>Th.</hi>) Of Juſtifying Faith; of the Nature &amp; Conditions of Chriſt. Faith 1631</item>
               <item>122 <hi>Kettlewell</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Diſcourſe of the Meaſures of Chriſtian Obedience 1684</item>
               <item>123 <hi>Lyford (W.)</hi> of Hereſy, with an Apology for our Publick Miniſtry, and Infant Bapt. 1657</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:46599:5"/>
               <item>124 <hi>Luther</hi>'s Commentary upon the 15 Pſalms, called <hi>Pſalmi Graduum Lond.</hi> 1577</item>
               <item>125 <hi>Lightfoot</hi>'s Harmony, Chronicle and Order of the Old Teſt. and 4 Evangeliſts 1647</item>
               <item>126 Morning Exerciſe at <hi>Cripplegate,</hi> &amp;c. By ſundry Miniſters, 4th Edition 1677</item>
               <item>127 —Supplement to the Morning Exerciſe at <hi>Cripplegate,</hi> &amp;c. 2d Edition 1676</item>
               <item>128 <hi>Moulin</hi>'s <hi>(P.)</hi> Vind. of the ſincerity of the Proteſtant Relig. in point of Obedience 1679</item>
               <item>129 —Buckler of the Faith; againſt the Objections of Mr. <hi>Arnoux</hi> the Jeſuit 1631</item>
               <item>130 <hi>Nicholſon</hi>'s (Bp) Expoſition of the Catechiſm of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>131 <hi>Napier</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> plain diſcovery of the whole Revelation of St. <hi>John</hi> 1645</item>
               <item>132 <hi>Owen</hi> (Dr. <hi>John</hi>) Doctrine of Juſtification by Faith, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> Explained, Confir<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>med, and Vindicated 1677</item>
               <item>133 —his Anſwer to Dr. <hi>Stillingfleet</hi>'s Unreaſonableneſs of Separation 1611</item>
               <item>134 <hi>Parker</hi> (Dr. <hi>Sam.</hi>) Authority of the Law of Nature, and of the Chriſtian Religion 1681</item>
               <item>135 <hi>Pierce</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Th.</hi>) Sermons on ſeveral Occaſions, before the King, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> in 2 vol. 1671-9</item>
               <item>136 <hi>Preſton</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> New Covenant, and Saints daily Exerciſe, in 7 Sermons 1631</item>
               <item>137 <hi>Perkin</hi>'s <hi>(W.)</hi> Cloud of Witneſſes; or Comment upon 11th to the <hi>Hebrews</hi> 1608</item>
               <item>138 <hi>Raleigh</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Walt.</hi>) Diſcourſes and Sermons on ſeveral Subjects 1679</item>
               <item>139 <hi>Reynold</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> 3 Treatiſes; Vanity of the Creature, ſinfulneſs of Sin, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1642</item>
               <item>140 <hi>Rutherford</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.)</hi> Plea for <hi>Paul</hi>'s Presbytery in <hi>Scotland Lond.</hi> 1642</item>
               <item>141 <hi>Roger's (Th.)</hi> Expoſition on the 39 Articles of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1625</item>
               <item>142 <hi>Simon</hi>'s (Father) Critical Enquiries into the various Editions of the Bible, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>143 Scripture Sufficiency, practically demonſtrated 1684</item>
               <item>144 <hi>Stillingfleet</hi> (Dr. <hi>Ed.</hi>) Unreaſonableneſs of Separation, <hi>&amp;c. Lond.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>145 —his <hi>Irenicum;</hi> a Weapon-Salve for the Churches Wounds 1662</item>
               <item>146 <hi>Smith</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Select Diſcourſes; with Dr. <hi>Patrick</hi>'s Account of his Life &amp; Death 1660</item>
               <item>147 <hi>Sympſon</hi>'s <hi>(A.)</hi> Expoſition upon the 2d Epiſtle of St. <hi>Peter</hi> 1632</item>
               <item>148 <hi>Sherlock (R.)</hi> againſt the Quakers; with brief Anſwers to their wild Queſtions 1656</item>
               <item>149 <hi>Sharp</hi>'s <hi>(L.)</hi> Looking-glaſs for the Pope, with the Pope's new Creed 1616</item>
               <item>150 <hi>Thorndike (H.)</hi> Juſt Weights and Meaſures; or ſtate of Relig. weighed, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>151 <hi>Teniſon</hi> (Dr. <hi>Tho.</hi>) of Idolatry; a Diſcourſe of its Notion, Cauſe, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>152 <hi>Turner</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Serm. before Sir <hi>P. Ward,</hi> with Addit. and 3 digreſſional Exercitat. 1689</item>
               <item>153 <hi>Wood</hi>'s <hi>(Ja.)</hi> Examination and Refutatation of Mr. <hi>Lockyer,</hi> about the Matter of the Viſible Church 1654</item>
               <item>154 Apocrypha, in a large Roman Letter <hi>Camb.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>155 Hiſtory of the Euchariſt; By <hi>Mons' L' Arro<expan>
                        <am>
                           <g ref="char:abque"/>
                        </am>
                        <ex>que</ex>
                     </expan>
                  </hi> Engliſh'd by <hi>J. W.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>156 Dr. <hi>Walt. Raleigh</hi>'s Diſcourſes and Sermons on ſeveral Subjects 1679</item>
               <item>157 <hi>H. Thorndike</hi>'s Juſt Weights and Meaſures; or ſtate of Relig. weighed, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>158 <hi>Caryll</hi> on the 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, &amp; 26 Chapt. of <hi>Job,</hi> in 3 vol. <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>159 Bp <hi>Coſin</hi>'s Scholaſtical Hiſtory of the Cannon of the Holy Scripture 1684</item>
               <item>160 <hi>P. Du-Moulin</hi>'s Vind. of the Proteſtant Religion, in the Point of Obedience, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>161 <hi>Jer. Burrough's</hi> Rare Jewel of Chriſtian Contentment 1670</item>
               <item>162 <hi>Clement</hi>'s firſt Epiſtle to the <hi>Corinthians,</hi> with learned Annotations 1647</item>
               <item>163 Dr. <hi>Ed. Stillingfleet</hi>'s <hi>Irenicum;</hi> A Weapon-Salve for the Churches Wounds 1661</item>
               <item>164 <hi>Edw. Elton</hi>'s Expoſition upon the Ten Commandments, and Lord's Prayer 1647</item>
               <item>165 Expoſition upon the Catechiſm of the Church of <hi>England.</hi> By Bp <hi>Nicholſon. London.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>166 Bible, with Service, Apochrypha, and Singing Pſalms <hi>Oxon.</hi>
               </item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="list">
            <pb n="3" facs="tcp:46599:5"/>
            <head>Divinity in Octavo.</head>
            <list>
               <item>167 APology of the Church of <hi>England.</hi> By Bp <hi>Jewel</hi> (with his Life) 1685</item>
               <item>168 Art of Contentment. By the Authr of the whole Duty of Man, <hi>&amp;c. Oxon.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>169 Animadverſions on a Treatiſe, intituled, The Proteſtant Reconciler 1683</item>
               <item>170 <hi>Amyraldus</hi> of Religion, refuting the Opinion that all are indifferent 1660</item>
               <item>171 Ancient Ceremonies, Hiſtorical Account of their Riſe, firſt entrance into the Ch. 1668</item>
               <item>172 Advice to the Conformiſts, and Nonconformiſts, for behaving themſelves, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>173 <hi>Aſhton (Will.)</hi> his Apology for the Honours and Revenues of the Clergy 1676</item>
               <item>174 <hi>Armitage (Tim.)</hi> Trial of Faith, or the Woman of <hi>Canaan,</hi> on <hi>Mat.</hi> 15.21, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>175 <hi>Allen</hi>'s <hi>(R.)</hi> Rebuke to Backſliders, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> in ſeveral Sermons 1684</item>
               <item>176 —<hi>Vindiciae Pietatis;</hi> or, a Vindication of Godlineſs, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>177 —Godly Fear, or the Nature and Neceſſity of Fear, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>178 <hi>Alleins</hi>'s <hi>(Joſ.)</hi> Alarm to unconverted Sinners, with Caſes of Conſcience 1678</item>
               <item>179 —Familiar Explanation of the Aſſemblies ſhorter Catechiſm 1682</item>
               <item>180 <hi>Allen</hi>'s <hi>(W.)</hi> Perſwaſive to Peace and Unity among Chriſtians 1672</item>
               <item>181 Aſſemblies ſhorter Catechiſm: A ſhort and plain Explication thereof 1675</item>
               <item>182 <hi>Bury</hi>'s Conſtant Communicant: or, indiſpenſible Duty of receiving the Sacrament 1681</item>
               <item>183 <hi>Burton</hi> (Dr. <hi>Hez.</hi>) Diſcourſes of Purity and Charity, Repentance, &amp;c. 1684</item>
               <item>174 <hi>Burnett</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Gilb.</hi>) Abridgment of his Hiſtory of the Reformation, &amp;c. 1683</item>
               <item>185 —Hiſtory of the Rights of Princes in diſpoſing of Church-Lands, &amp;c. 1682</item>
               <item>186 —Remarks on the Letter of the Clergy of <hi>France</hi> to the Proteſtants 1683</item>
               <item>187 —Vindication of the Ordination of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>188 <hi>Bagſhaw</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Hen.</hi>) Select Diſcourſes againſt Papiſts and Socinians 1680</item>
               <item>189 <hi>Barrow</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Iſ.</hi>) Sermons of Contentment, Patience, &amp;c. to the Will of God 1685</item>
               <item>190 —Sermon at the Spittal, of Duty, and Reward of Bounty to the Poor 1671</item>
               <item>191 <hi>Baxter</hi>'s <hi>(R.)</hi> Political Aphoriſms, opening the true Principles of Government 1659</item>
               <item>192 —True and only way of Concord of all the Chriſtian Churches 1680</item>
               <item>193 —Third Defence of the Cauſe of Peace, againſt <hi>J. Hinckley</hi> and others 1681</item>
               <item>194 —Compaſſionate Counſel to all young Men 1681</item>
               <item>195 —Poor Man's Family-Book, with a Form of Exhortation to the Sick 1680</item>
               <item>196 —Catechiſing of Families: A Teacher of Houſholders to teach their Houſholds</item>
               <item>197 —Directions for getting and keeping Spiritual Peace and Comfort 1669</item>
               <item>198 —Two Diſcourſes of the Immortality of Man, and Nature of it, &amp;c. 1682</item>
               <item>199 —Directions and Perſwaſions to a ſound Converſion 1670</item>
               <item>200 Bible, with the ſinging Pſalms, and References in the Marg. (gilt Edges) <hi>Lond.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>201 —Another, with Common-Prayer, ſinging Pſalms — (gilt Edges) <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>202 Book of Common-Prayer, with Cuts, of a large Roman Letter, and rul'd, (Turky, and Gilt) 1662</item>
               <item>203 <hi>Bates</hi> (Dr. <hi>W.</hi>) Sermon at the Funeral of Dr. <hi>Manton,</hi> with Dr. <hi>Manton</hi>'s laſt Sermon.</item>
               <item>204 <hi>Bolton</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Sam.</hi>) true Bounds of <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> Freedom, &amp;c. 1656</item>
               <item>205 <hi>Ball</hi>'s Catechiſm; or a Treatiſe of the principal Grounds of Chriſtian Religion 1670</item>
               <item>206 <hi>Brevint</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Dan.</hi>) Depth and Myſtery of Roman Maſs, laid open, &amp;c. <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>207 —<hi>Saul</hi> and <hi>Samuel</hi> at <hi>Endor,</hi> or the new Ways of Salvation, &amp;c. to <hi>Rome</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>208 <hi>Bunnyon (John)</hi> Sighs from Hell, or the Groans of a damned Soul <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>209 —Holy War made upon <hi>Diabolus,</hi> &amp;c. for taking the Town of Man-ſoul 1682</item>
               <item>210 <hi>B—(R.)</hi> his choice Emblems, Divine and Moral, ingraven on Copper Plates 1684</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:46599:6"/>
               <item>211 Bp <hi>Bedell</hi>'s Life, with Copies of the Letters between him &amp; Mr. <hi>Waddeſworth</hi> about Relig.</item>
               <item>212 Beauty of Holineſs; in a Diſcourſe by the Author of the whole Duty of Man, &amp;c. 1680</item>
               <item>213 Lady <hi>Brook</hi>'s Life, with a Sermon at her Funeral. By <hi>N. Parkhurſt</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>214 <hi>Brook</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Precious Remedies againſt Satan's Devices 1662</item>
               <item>215 <hi>Burrough</hi>'s <hi>(Jer.) Moſes</hi> his Self-denial, on <hi>Heb.</hi> 11.24. 1641</item>
               <item>216 <hi>Bridg</hi>'s <hi>(W.)</hi> Sermons, of the Freeneſs of the Grace and Love of God 1671</item>
               <item>217 <hi>Comber</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>T.</hi>) Companion to the Altar; with an Eſſay upon Baptiſm, Catech, &amp;c. 1685</item>
               <item>218 —Companion to the Temple; or, a Help to Devotion, in 2 vol. 1679</item>
               <item>219 <hi>Cave</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>W.</hi>) Primitive Chriſtianity; or, the Religion of Ancient Chriſtians 1682</item>
               <item>220 —Diſſertation concerning the Government of the Ancient Church 1683</item>
               <item>221 <hi>Cave (John)</hi> Goſpel preached to the Romans; in 4 Sermons 1681</item>
               <item>222 Critical Hiſtory of the Religions and Cuſtoms of the Eeſtern Nations 1685</item>
               <item>223 <hi>Cotton</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Expoſition, with practical Obſervations upon <hi>Eccleſiaſies</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>224 <hi>Coſin</hi>'s (Bp) Opinion for communicating with <hi>Geneva</hi> rather than <hi>Rome</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>225 <hi>Cardan</hi> his three Books of Conſolation, Engliſhed; of great uſe 1683</item>
               <item>226 Common-Prayer Book, of a fair Character, (in Turky, and Gilt) 12<hi>o Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>227 <hi>Drelincourt</hi> (Mr.) Chriſtian Defence againſt the Fears of Death 1682</item>
               <item>228 <hi>Dunton</hi>'s Remains: or, the dying Paſtor's laſt Legacy, &amp;c. (with Cuts) 1684</item>
               <item>229 —Pilgrim's Gude, from the Cradle to his Death-bed (with Copper Cuts) 1684</item>
               <item>230 Diſcourſe concerning the Trial of Spirits. By Dr, <hi>Tho. Pittis</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>231 Diſcourſe concerning Evangelical Love, Church-Peace and Unity 1672</item>
               <item>232 Diſcourſes upon Select Texts, againſt Papiſts and Socinians. By Dr. <hi>Bagſhaw</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>233 <hi>Deering</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Sermon before Q. <hi>Elizabeth,</hi> with other Serm. and godly Treatiſes 1569</item>
               <item>234 <hi>Davenport (John)</hi> Power of Congregational Churches, Aſſerted &amp; Vindicated 1672</item>
               <item>235 Diſcourſe about pretending Religious aſſembling in private Conventicles 1685</item>
               <item>236 —About the Worſhip of God, towards the Table, or Altar 1682</item>
               <item>237 <hi>Doolittle (Th.)</hi> Spiritual Antidote againſt ſinful Contagion, &amp;c. 1667</item>
               <item>238 —Directions how to live after a waſting Plague 1666</item>
               <item>239 <hi>Dickson</hi>'s <hi>(Dav.)</hi> Expoſition of St. <hi>Matthew</hi>'s Goſpel, third Edition 1651</item>
               <item>240 Doctrine of the Church of <hi>England,</hi> about the Lord's Day, or Sabbath 1683</item>
               <item>241 <hi>Everard</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>John</hi>) Works of Chriſt's Sufferings, &amp;c. in ſeveral Sermons 1659</item>
               <item>242 <hi>England</hi>'s Imminent Danger, and only Remedy, faithfully conſider'd, &amp;c. 1682</item>
               <item>143 Enter into the Cloſet; or Method and Order for Private Devotion 1684</item>
               <item>244 Enquiry after Happineſs. By <hi>R. Lucas Lond.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>245 <hi>England</hi>'s Vanity: or, God's Voice againſt Pride in Dreſs and Apparel 1683</item>
               <item>246 <hi>Fowler</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Deſign of Chriſtianity, 2d Edition 1676</item>
               <item>247 <hi>Fuller</hi>'s <hi>(Ignat.)</hi> 3 Sermons of Peace and Holineſs, on ſeveral Occaſions 1672</item>
               <item>248 <hi>Fenner</hi>'s <hi>(W.)</hi> Divine Meſſage to the Elect Soul, in 8 Sermons 1676</item>
               <item>249 <hi>Flavell</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Divine Conduct: or, the Myſtery of Providence 1678</item>
               <item>250 —Token for Mourners; or Chriſt's Advice to a diſtreſſed Mother, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>251 —Saint indeed; or the great Work of a Chriſtian opened, &amp;c. 1677</item>
               <item>252 —Navigation Spiritualiz'd: or, a new Compaſs for Sea-men 1677</item>
               <item>253 <hi>Fuller</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Th.</hi>) Triple Reconciler: w<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="3 letters">
                     <desc>•••</desc>
                  </gap> a Serm. on the day of the King's Inaugurat.</item>
               <item>254 Fort-Royal of Holy Scriptures: or, a new Concordance, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> By <hi>J. H.</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>255 Government of the Tongue. By the Author of the whole Duty of Man, &amp;c. 1675</item>
               <item>256 Gentleman's Calling, by the ſame Author <hi>Lond.</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>257 <hi>Gauden</hi>'s (Dr.) Diſcourſe of Artificial Hanſomneſs, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> between two Ladies 1656</item>
               <item>258 Great Evil and Miſchief of Health-drinking; with Antidotes againſt it 1684</item>
               <item>259 God's Voice againſt the monſtrous Sin of Pride, in Dreſs and Apparel 1683</item>
               <pb n="4" facs="tcp:46599:6"/>
               <item>260 <hi>Graile (J.)</hi> his four Sermons upon ſeveral occaſions at <hi>Norwich,</hi> &amp;c. <hi>Lond.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>261 <hi>Greenhill</hi>'s Treatiſe of ſoundneſs of Heart; with other Sermons 1670</item>
               <item>262 <hi>Gouge</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Chriſtian Diaections how to walk with God all the day 1684</item>
               <item>263 —Young Man's Guide through the Wilderneſs of this World, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>264 —Principles of Chriſtian Religion explained, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> Or his Catechiſm 1684</item>
               <item>265 Harmony of Natural and Poſitive Divine Laws <hi>Lond.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>366 <hi>Hockin (Tho.)</hi> his Diſcourſe of the Nature of God's Decrees 1684</item>
               <item>267 <hi>Hale</hi>'s (Judg) Contemplations Moral and Divine 1677</item>
               <item>268 <hi>Hopkins</hi> (Bp <hi>Ez.</hi>) Vanity of the World, with other Sermons 1685</item>
               <item>269 <hi>Horn (Jo.)</hi> his Eſſays about general and ſpecial Grace 1685</item>
               <item>270 <hi>Hierocles</hi> upon the Golden Verſes of the <hi>Pythagorians</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>271 Harbinger for the King of Glory: A Treatiſe on <hi>Luke</hi> 1.17. <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>272 Health-drinking: A Diſcourſe of the great Evil and Miſchief thereof 1684</item>
               <item>273 <hi>Hooke (W.)</hi> Priviledg of the Saints on Earth, beyond thoſe in Heaven 1673</item>
               <item>274 Hiſtory of the young converted Gallant (a Divine Poem, by <hi>B. Keach</hi>) 1679</item>
               <item>275 Holy Inquiſition; or dealing of the Ch. of <hi>Rome</hi> with thoſe that diſſent from it 1681</item>
               <item>276 <hi>Howe (John)</hi> his Treatiſe of delighting in God; from <hi>Pſal.</hi> 37.4. 1674</item>
               <item>277 —Bleſſedneſs of the Righteous opened, in two Treatiſes 1673</item>
               <item>278 <hi>Horneck</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Anth.</hi>) Proſpect of the great Day of Judgment 1684</item>
               <item>279 <hi>Hardcaſtle</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Chriſtian Geography and Arith. in ſeveral Sermons 1674</item>
               <item>280 Hiſtory of ancient Ceremonies; of their firſt entrance into the Church, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>281 <hi>Jewel</hi>'s (Bp) Apology of the Church of <hi>England</hi> (with the ſaid Biſhop's Life) 1685</item>
               <item>282 Juſtice of Peace his Calling: A Moral Eſſay, with a Prayer 1684</item>
               <item>283 <hi>Janeway</hi>'s <hi>(Ja.)</hi> Beſt Friend in the worſt of Times, in ſeveral Sermons 1677</item>
               <item>284 <hi>Jones (J.)</hi> Great Duty of Conformity plainly illuſtrated in an Example 1684</item>
               <item>285 <hi>Kidder</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Diſcourſe concerning the Grounds of Chriſtian Fortitude 1680</item>
               <item>286 Ladies Calling; by the Author of the <hi>Whole Duty of Man,</hi> &amp;c. <hi>Oxf.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>287 Lively Oracles given to us, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> By the ſame Author <hi>ibid.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>288 Letter from <hi>R. Smith</hi> to Dr. <hi>Hammond,</hi> with the Drs. Anſ. about Chriſt's Diſc. into Hell</item>
               <item>289 <hi>Lowth (Sim.)</hi> of the Subject of Church-power, in whom it reſides 1685</item>
               <item>290 <hi>Lucas</hi> (Mr. <hi>A.</hi>) his enquiry after Happineſs <hi>Lond.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>291 <hi>Lane</hi>'s <hi>(Moſes)</hi> Proteſt. School; with Account of Plots, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> ſince Q. <hi>Eliz.</hi> (with fig.) 1681</item>
               <item>292 <hi>Lockier</hi>'s Memorial of God's Judgments, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> in ſeveral Sermons 1671</item>
               <item>293 <hi>Luther</hi>'s <hi>(M.)</hi> 34 ſpecial and choſen Sermons 1649</item>
               <item>294 Life of God in the Soul of Man: Or Nature and Excellency of the Chriſt. Relig. 1677</item>
               <item>295 Life of <hi>W. Bedell,</hi> D. D. Biſhop of <hi>Kilmore</hi> in <hi>Ireland</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>296 —And Death of the Earl of <hi>Rocheſter.</hi> By Dr. <hi>Gilb. Burnet</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>297 —Of the Lady <hi>Eliz. Brooks,</hi> with her Funeral Sermon. By <hi>N. Parkhurſt</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>298 —Of Dr. <hi>Pet. Heylin;</hi> with an Anſwer to <hi>Baxter</hi>'s falſe Accuſations 1683</item>
               <item>299 —Of <hi>Cl. Fl. Julian</hi> the Apoſtate; with Reflect. on <hi>Johnſon</hi>'s Accunt of <hi>Julian</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>300 —Of <hi>James Janeway</hi> Miniſter of the Goſpel 1678</item>
               <item>301 —Of Dr. <hi>Sam. Winter,</hi> ſometime Provoſt of Trinity Colledg in <hi>Ireland</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>302 —Of <hi>Galeacius Caracciolus;</hi> or the <hi>Italian</hi> Convert (with fig.) 1677</item>
               <item>303 Moderation of the Church of <hi>England.</hi> By Dr. <hi>Puller</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>304 <hi>Maurice</hi>'s (Dr.) Vindicat. of the Primitive Church, againſt <hi>Baxter</hi>'s Church Hiſt. 1682</item>
               <item>305 <hi>Manton</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Tho.</hi>) Practical Expoſition of the Lord's-Prayer 1684</item>
               <item>306 <hi>Mamburg</hi> of the Prerogatives of the Church of <hi>Rome,</hi> and her Biſhops 1685</item>
               <item>307 Mother's Legacy to her unborn Children. By <hi>Elizabeth Joceline</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>308 <hi>Manningham (Tho.)</hi> His two Diſcourſes againſt Popiſh Doctrines, &amp;c. 1681</item>
               <item>309 Manual of Devotion. By a Miniſter under apprehenſion of the Stone 1683</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:46599:7"/>
               <item>310 <hi>Norris (John)</hi> his Diſcourſe about the pretended Religious Aſſemblies in the P. Conventicles <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>311 <hi>Northbrook (J.)</hi> Poor Man's Garden, for Flowers of the Scriptures, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1600</item>
               <item>312 <hi>Nalſon</hi>'s true Liberty and Dominion of Conſcience vindicated 1678</item>
               <item>313 <hi>Neſſe</hi>'s <hi>(Ch.)</hi> Chriſtians Walk and Works on Earth, until to Heaven 1678</item>
               <item>314 —Compleat and compendious Church Hiſtory; ſecond Edition 1681</item>
               <item>315 <hi>Owen</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>J.</hi>) Diſcourſe about Evangelical Love, Church Peace and Unity 1672</item>
               <item>316 —Diſcourſe on the words of our Lord Jeſus Chriſt, on <hi>Luke</hi> 13.1, 2, 3, 4, 5. <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>317 —Cauſes, ways and means of underſtanding God's Mind 1678</item>
               <item>318 <hi>Outram</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>W.</hi>) Sermons upon Faith and Providence, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>319 Practice of Piety in a fair large Roman Letter <hi>Lond.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>320 Proteſtant School: Method for bring up and well-governing Children, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>321 Proteſtant and Popiſh Religion ſurvey'd; ſhewing their Irreconcileableneſs 1685</item>
               <item>322 Proteſtant Reconciler, pleading for Condeſcention to Diſſenters, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 2 vol. 1683</item>
               <item>323 —Animadverſions upon the Proteſtant Reconciler 1683</item>
               <item>324 <hi>Puller</hi> (Dr. <hi>Tim.</hi>) of Moderation of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>325 <hi>Parkhurſt</hi>'s <hi>(N.)</hi> Sermon at the Funeral of the Lady <hi>Eliz. Brook,</hi> with her Life 1684</item>
               <item>326 Peace and Holineſs; in 3 Sermons upon ſeveral occaſions: By <hi>Ig. Fuller</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>327 <hi>Pitti</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Tho.</hi>) his Diſcourſe concerning the Trial of Spirits 1683</item>
               <item>328 Pernicious Conſequences of the Hereſy of the Jeſuits againſt King and State 1666</item>
               <item>330 <hi>Patrick</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Sym.</hi>) Witneſſes to Chriſtianity in 2 vol. <hi>Lond.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>331 <hi>Pelling (Edw.)</hi> his Diſcourſe of the Sacrament of the Lord's-Supper 1685</item>
               <item>332 <hi>Parker</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Sam.</hi>) Diſcourſe of Eccleſiaſtical Polity 1671</item>
               <item>333 —Caſe of the Church of <hi>England,</hi> briefly and truly ſtated 1681</item>
               <item>334 —Reproof to the Rehearſal tranſproſed, againſt <hi>Marvel</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>335 <hi>Pool (Matth.)</hi> Nullity of the of Romiſh Faith, with an Appendix 1679</item>
               <item>336 Prerogatives of the Church of <hi>Rome,</hi> and her Biſhops 1685</item>
               <item>337 Plat for Mariners; or the Seaman's Preacher. By <hi>J. Ruther</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>338 <hi>Quarles (J.)</hi> Fountain of Tears, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> with an Elegy on Sir. <hi>Ch. Lucas</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>339 —Divine Meditations upon ſeveral Subjects, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>340 <hi>Roſs (Alex.)</hi> View of all Religions in the World, with the Lives, Actions, and Ends of notorious Hereticks, with their Effigies in Copper Plates. 1672</item>
               <item>341 <hi>Row</hi>'s <hi>(J.)</hi> XXX Sermons of Chriſt's Love in his Incarnation, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>342 <hi>Ryther</hi>'s <hi>(J.)</hi> Plat for Marriners, in ſeveral Sermons, upon <hi>Jonah</hi>'s Voyage 1675</item>
               <item>343 <hi>Resbury (R)</hi> Doctrine of Election and Reprobation. In ſix Sermons againſt <hi>Armin.</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>344 Remains of <hi>John Dunton:</hi> Or, the dying Paſtor's laſt Legacy, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> (with Figures) 1684</item>
               <item>345 Riſe and growth of the firſt Church of God. Deſcribed by <hi>Th. Tanner.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>346 <hi>Raits (W.)</hi> Vindication of the Reformed Religion, from the Reflections of a Romaniſt. 1671</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Simon</hi>'s (Father) Hiſtory of the Original and Progreſs of Eccleſiaſtical Revenues. 1685</item>
               <item>— Critical Hiſtory of the Religions and Cuſtoms of the Eaſtern Nations. 1685</item>
               <item>347 <hi>Seller</hi>'s <hi>(A.)</hi> Remarks relating to the State of the Church, and againſt <hi>J. Hanmer.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>348 <hi>Stratford</hi> (Dr. <hi>Nich.</hi>) Diſſwaſive from Revenge. <hi>London.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>349 <hi>Sherlock</hi> (Dr. <hi>William</hi>) Practical Diſcourſe of Religious Aſſemblies 1682</item>
               <item>350 —Diſcourſe about Church Unity in Defence of Dr. <hi>Stillingfleet</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>351 <hi>Stillingfleet</hi>'s (Dr.) Anſwer to <hi>Creſſy</hi>'s Epiſt. Apologetical to Lord <hi>Hide</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>352 —Diſcourſe concerning the Idolatry practiſed in the Church of <hi>Rome</hi> 1676</item>
               <pb n="5" facs="tcp:46599:7"/>
               <item>353 <hi>Spurſtow</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>W.</hi>) ſix Decads of Divine Meditations on ſeveral Subjects — <hi>Lond.</hi> 1666</item>
               <item>354 <hi>Smith (John)</hi> Of King <hi>Solomons</hi> Portraiture of Old Age. 1666</item>
               <item>355 <hi>Seldens (Jn.)</hi> Tract proving the Nativity of Chriſt to be on the 25th. of <hi>Decemb.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>356 <hi>Shepard's (Th.)</hi> Sound Believer. Or Treatiſe of Evangelical Converſion. 1671</item>
               <item>357 <hi>Steele (R.)</hi> Of the Trades-mans Calling. Or a Diſcourſe of a calling in general 1684</item>
               <item>358 <hi>Standfaſt's (R.)</hi> Little handful of Cordial Comforts, and a Caveat againſt Seducers 1684</item>
               <item>359 <hi>Smith's (R.)</hi> Letter about Chriſts Deſcention into Hell, with Dr. <hi>Hammonds</hi> Anſwer 1684</item>
               <item>360 Satan's Methods and Malice baſſled by Mrs. <hi>Hannah Allen</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>361 <hi>Saywell</hi> (Dr. <hi>W.</hi>) Of Evangelical and Catholick Unity, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>362 <hi>Smith (Miles)</hi> His Tranſlation of the Pſalms into <hi>Engliſh</hi> Verſe 1668</item>
               <item>363 <hi>Shaw's (S.)</hi> True Chriſtians Teſt, or diſcovery of the Love and Lovers of the world 1682</item>
               <item>364 <hi>Sandy's (Geo.)</hi> Paraphraſe upon the Pſalms, with Muſical Notes 1676</item>
               <item>365 <hi>Sanderſons</hi> (Bp.) Nine Caſes of Conſcience Occaſionally Determined 1685</item>
               <item>366 <hi>Tanners (Th.)</hi> Riſe and Growth of the firſt Church of God deſcribed 1683</item>
               <item>367 <hi>Tillotſon's</hi> (Dr.) Rule of Faith: or an Anſwer to <hi>Sergeant's</hi> ſure-footing 1676</item>
               <item>368 <hi>Troughton's (Jn.) Lutherus Redevivus:</hi> or Vindication of Proteſtant Doctrin, 2 Vol. 1677</item>
               <item>369 Treatiſe of Baptiſme, by Anonymous Author 1646</item>
               <item>370 <hi>Thomas (W)</hi> His familiar Inſtructions in the Reſolving of Scripture Queſtions 1684</item>
               <item>371 <hi>Turner (John)</hi> His Diſcourſe concerning the Meſſias, in 3 Chapters 1685</item>
               <item>372 — Apologetical Vindication of the middle way betwixt Neceſſity and Freedom 1683</item>
               <item>373 <hi>Thomſon (Sam.)</hi> His Exercitations and Meditations on ſome Texts of H. Script. 1676</item>
               <item>374 <hi>Trahern's Roman</hi> Forgeries: Diſcovering the Impoſtures, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of the Ch. of <hi>Rome</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>375 <hi>Taylor's (Nath.)</hi> Expoſition of the Catechiſm of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>376 Triumphs of Chriſtianity: or the Life of <hi>Julian</hi> the Apoſtate 1683</item>
               <item>377 Vanity of the Creature. By the Author of the whole Duty of Man, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>378 <hi>Vincent's (Nath.)</hi> Diſcourſe of the Spirit of Prayer 1677</item>
               <item>379 Diſcourſe concerning Love 1684</item>
               <item>380 <hi>Virel's (Math.)</hi> Treatiſe of the principal grounds of Chriſtian Religion 1612</item>
               <item>381 Voice of God againſt the Monſtrous ſin of Pride in Dreſs and Apparel 1683</item>
               <item>382 <hi>Vines (R.)</hi> Treatiſe of the Sacrament of the Lords Supper, in XX. Sermons 1677</item>
               <item>383 <hi>Venning (Ralph)</hi> Sermons of Sin, and the Plague thereof 1669</item>
               <item>384 — Milk and Honey, with a 2d Part of Orthodox Paradoxes 1654</item>
               <item>385 Unreaſonableneſs of the Romaniſts, requiring our Communion with them 1670</item>
               <item>386 <hi>Uſher's</hi> (Bp.) Proteſtant-School, with Account of Plots ſince Q. <hi>Eliz.</hi> with Fig. 1681</item>
               <item>387 <hi>Stockton's (O.)</hi> Warning to Drunkards, in ſeveral Sermons 1682</item>
               <item>388 Survey and Compariſon of the Proteſtant Religion with Popery 1685</item>
               <item>389 <hi>Squire</hi> (Mr.) Unreaſonableneſs of the Romaniſts, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>390 Whole Duty of Man (the Author of the) all his Works in 5 Vol.</item>
               <item>391 Whole Duty of Man. The 2d. Part 1683</item>
               <item>392 <hi>Wilkin's</hi> (Bp.) Of the Principles and Duties of Natural Religion 1678</item>
               <item>393 —Diſcourſe concerning the Gift of Preaching, 6th Edition 1679</item>
               <item>394 —His Sermons Preached upon ſeveral occaſions 1682</item>
               <item>395 <hi>White (Jn.)</hi> His Directions for the Profitable Reading of the Scriptures 1647</item>
               <item>396 <hi>Whiſton (Joſ.)</hi> Infant Baptiſm plainly proved 1678</item>
               <item>397 <hi>Ward</hi>'s (Bp.) ſeven Sermons at <hi>White-Hall,</hi> and before the Houſe of Peers 1679</item>
               <item>398 <hi>Whetenall's</hi> (Bp.) Method and Order for Private Devotion 1684</item>
               <item>399 <hi>Winſt<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="5 letters">
                        <desc>•••••</desc>
                     </gap> (Ger<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ard)</hi> Of fulfilling of Propheſies, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1648</item>
               <item>400 Way to Comfort in ſuffering Times, with the Hiſtory of Chriſts Sufferings, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>401 <hi>Wilkinſon's</hi> (Dr.) Two Treatiſes of God's All-ſufficiency and Chriſts preciouſneſs 1681</item>
               <item>402 <hi>Watſon (Th.)</hi> On the Beatitudes: or Diſcourſe on Chriſts Sermon on the Mount 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <pb facs="tcp:46599:8"/>
               <item>403 —Heaven taken by Storm: or Violence of a Chriſtian after Glory <hi>Lond.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>404 Way to Chriſt, and a glimpſe of Heavens Glory, by <hi>T. J.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>405 Bible with References in the Margent (neatly Bound in Turky Leather) 1676</item>
               <item>406 <hi>Burton's</hi> (Dr. <hi>Ez.</hi>) Diſcourſes of Purity and Charity, Repentance, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 2 Vol. 1684</item>
               <item>407 Bp. <hi>Jewels</hi> Apology of the Church of <hi>England,</hi> (with the Bps. Life) 1685</item>
               <item>408 Dr. <hi>Bury's</hi> Conſtant Communicant, or Indiſpenſible Duty of Receiving the Sacra. 1681</item>
               <item>409 <hi>Dun<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>on's</hi> Remains: Or, the Dying Paſtor's laſt Legacy, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> with Cuts 1684</item>
               <item>410 Proteſtant Reconciler, pleading for Condeſcention to Diſſenters, in 2 Vol. 1683</item>
               <item>411 Lively Oracles given to us, by the Author of the whole Duty of Man 1678</item>
               <item>412 Dr. <hi>Puller</hi> of the Moderation of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>413 <hi>Ig. Fuller's</hi> 3 Sermons upon ſeveral occaſions of Peace and Holineſs 1672</item>
               <item>414 Principles and Duties of Natural Religion, by Bp. <hi>Wilkins</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>415 Vanity of the Creature, by the Author of the whole Duty of Man, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>416 Dr. <hi>Tillo<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ſon's</hi> Rule of Faith: with Dr. <hi>Stillingfleets</hi> Reply to <hi>J. Sergeant</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>417 Dr. <hi>Bagſhaw's</hi> Diſcourſes upon Select Texts againſt Papiſts and Socinians 1680</item>
               <item>418 Dr. <hi>Cave's</hi> Primitive Chriſtianity: or Religion of the Ancient Chriſtians 1682</item>
               <item>419 —Diſcourſe of the Ancient Church-Government 1683</item>
               <item>420 Dr. <hi>Everard's</hi> Sermons; with the Myſtical Divinity of <hi>Dionyſius</hi> the <hi>Areopagite</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>421 The Goſpel preached to the <hi>Romans</hi> in four Sermons, by <hi>John Cave</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>422 Diſcourſe about Evangelical Love, Church peace and Unity, by Dr. <hi>Owen</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>423 Naked Breaſts and Shoulders, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> or God's Voice againſt pride in dreſs, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>424 Compaſſionate Counſel to all young Men, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>R. Baxter</hi>
               </item>
               <item>425 <hi>M. Amyraldus</hi> of Religions, refuting the opinion that all are Indifferent 1660</item>
               <item>426 Vindication of the Primitive Church, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> againſt <hi>Baxter;</hi> by Dr. <hi>Morice</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>427 <hi>Sim. Lowth</hi> of the Subject of Church power, in whom it reſides 1685</item>
               <item>428 Critical Hiſtory of the Religions and Cuſtoms of the <hi>Eaſtern</hi> Nations 1685</item>
               <item>429 Dr. <hi>Wilkinſon</hi>'s Sermons about God's All ſufficiency and Chriſts Preciouſneſs 1681</item>
               <item>430 Vindication of the Ordinations of the Church of <hi>England,</hi> by Dr. <hi>Burnet</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>431 Companion to the Altar. An help to the Worthy Receiv. the Sacra. by Dr. <hi>Comber</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>432 Divine Conduct: or the Myſteries of Providence, by <hi>Jn. Flavel</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>433 Diſcourſe againſt Religious Aſſembling in private Conventicles, by <hi>J. N.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>434 <hi>J. Row's</hi> XXX Sermons of Chr<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ſt's Love in his Incarnation, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>43<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> Divine Meſſage to the Elect Soul in 8 Sermons, by <hi>W. Fenner</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>436 Trades-mans Calling and directions for the right Managing, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>R. Steel</hi> 1689</item>
               <item>437 Bp. <hi>C<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ſi<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>'s</hi> Opinion for Communicating rather with <hi>Geneva</hi> then <hi>Rome</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>438 <hi>Th. Sh<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>pard's</hi> ſound Believer A Treatiſe of Evangelical Converſion 1671</item>
               <item>439 Unreaſonableneſs of the Romaniſts; requiring our Communion with them 1670</item>
               <item>440 Bp. <hi>Sanderſon's</hi> nine caſes of Conſcience<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> occaſionally determined 1685</item>
               <item>441 Diſcourſe of the Spirit of Prayer, by <hi>Nath. Vincent</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>442 Family Inſtructions in reſolving of Scripture Queſtions, by <hi>W. Thomas</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>443 Dr <hi>Burnet's</hi> Hiſtory of the Rights of Princes in diſpoſing of Church-Land, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>444 — Abridgment of the Hiſt of the Reformation of the Church of <hi>Eng.</hi> (with Fig) 1683</item>
               <item>445 — Anſwer to the Clergy of <hi>France</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>446 Diſcourſe of the Nature of God s Decrees, by <hi>Th. H<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ckin</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>447 Riſe and growth of the fi<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ſt Church of God, deſcribed by <hi>T. Tanner</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>448 Remarks relating to the ſtate of the Church of the firſt Centuries, by <hi>A. S.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>449 Diſſwaſive from Revenge, in a Diſcourſe upon <hi>Rom.</hi> 12.17. by Dr. <hi>Stratford</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>450 Vanity of the world, with other Sermons, by Biſhop <hi>Hopkins</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>451 <hi>Hierocles</hi> upon the Golden Verſes of the <hi>Pythagoreans</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>452 <hi>R. Smith</hi>'s Letter about Chriſts Deſcention into Hell, with Dr. <hi>Hammond</hi>'s Anſw. 1684</item>
               <pb n="6" facs="tcp:46599:8"/>
               <item>453 Priviledg of the Saints on Earth beyond thoſe in Heaven, by <hi>W. Hooke Lond.</hi> 1673</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="list">
            <head>Divinity in <hi>Twelves,</hi> &amp;c.</head>
            <list>
               <item>454 <hi>ABbot (Rob.)</hi> Young Mans Warning-piece, in the life of <hi>W. Rogers</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>455 <hi>Arminius</hi> his Judgment about the points of Religion declared, 1657</item>
               <item>456 <hi>Andrews</hi> (Bp.) pattern of Catechiſtical Doctrine, with Additions 1641</item>
               <item>457 — Manual of private Devotions, with a Mannal of directions for the ſick 1674</item>
               <item>458 <hi>Abercromby (D.)</hi> Proteſtancy to be embraced, (writ. 19 Ye. aft. his profeſ. of Po.) 1682</item>
               <item>459 Bible with Singing Pſalms, and References in the Marg. in 12<hi>s.</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>460 — Another with Com. Pray. and Sing. Pſalms (Turky and Gilt) 1682</item>
               <item>461 Book of Common Prayer with ſinging Pſalms, (Turky Gilt) in 12<hi>s.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>462 — Another in 12<hi>s,</hi> with the Singing Pſalms <hi>Oxf.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>463 — Another in 24<hi>s Lond.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>464 — Same again, with the New Teſtament and Pſalms</item>
               <item>464 <hi>B — (R.)</hi> Choice-Emblems Divine and Moral, engraven on Copper Plates 1684</item>
               <item>466 <hi>Berault</hi>'s <hi>(P.)</hi> True way to Heaven, in <hi>French</hi> and Engliſh (Turky Gilt) 1681</item>
               <item>467 <hi>Bunyan (John)</hi> Of the loſing and taking again the Town of <hi>Manſoul</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>468 — Life and death of Mr. <hi>Badman,</hi> in a familiar Dialogue 1680</item>
               <item>469 —Of the greatneſs of the Soul, and unſpeakableneſs of its Loſs 168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>470 <hi>Brook</hi>'s <hi>(Th.)</hi> Apples of Gold for Young Men and Women, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>471 <hi>Bona</hi>'s guide to Eternity, engliſhed by Sir <hi>R. L'Eſtrange</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>472 <hi>Baxters (R.)</hi> Sermon of Judgment 1668</item>
               <item>473 Beſt guide to Devotion, ſhort Prayers and Meditations to all occaſions 1685</item>
               <item>474 <hi>Bridges (W.)</hi> Word to the Aged 1668</item>
               <item>475 <hi>Cromptons (W.)</hi> Wilderneſs of trouble leading to a <hi>Canaan</hi> of comfort 1675</item>
               <item>476 Lord <hi>Capels</hi> excellent Contemplations Divine and Moral 1683</item>
               <item>477 Councils of Wiſdom, or a Collection of the Maxims of <hi>Solomon</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>478 Chriſtian Devotion, or a Manual of Prayers, illuſtrated with Sculptures 1679</item>
               <item>479 Cabinet of Jewels, or a glimpſe of <hi>Sions</hi> glory, by <hi>W. Dyer</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>480 <hi>Crompton</hi>'s <hi>(W.)</hi> Wilderneſs of trouble, leading to a <hi>Canaan</hi> of comfort 1679</item>
               <item>481 <hi>Colet</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>John</hi>) daily Devotions, digeſted into Prayers and Meditations 1684</item>
               <item>482 Chriſtians guide, with Meditations and Prayers to all occaſions 1683</item>
               <item>483 Chriſtian Diary, or brief directions for Devotion and Converſation 1684</item>
               <item>484 Common Prayer Book, with New Teſtament and Pſalms, in 24<hi>s</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>485 <hi>Dunton</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Houſe of weeping, or Mans laſt progreſs to his long Home 1682</item>
               <item>486 — Pil<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="3 letters">
                     <desc>•••</desc>
                  </gap>s guide from the Cradle to his death bed (with Cuts) 1684</item>
               <item>487 Daily Exerciſe for a Chriſtian or a Manual of private Devotions 1684</item>
               <item>488 <hi>Davids</hi> Bleſſed Man, or a ſhort Expoſition of the firſt Pſalm, by <hi>S. Smith</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>489 <hi>Drexelius</hi> his Conſiderations upon Eternity (with Copper Cuts) 1684</item>
               <item>490 Divine Art of Memory, or ſum of the Holy Scriptures in <hi>Acroſtick</hi> Ve<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ſes 1683</item>
               <item>491 Divine Love, or willingneſs of Chriſt to ſave ſinners, in Three Dialog<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>es 1677</item>
               <item>492 Daily Exerciſe of a devout Chriſtian, or a pract cal preparative to Devotion 1683</item>
               <item>493 Devout Communicant with Rules for worthy Receiving the Sacram. by <hi>A. Seller</hi> 1686</item>
               <item>494 Diſc. againſt Drunken. with 2 Serm. of St. <hi>Aug.</hi> about the ſame, by <hi>M Scrivener</hi>
               </item>
               <item>495 <hi>Dunton</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Heavenly Paſtime, Obſerv. on remarkable paſſages in the Bible 1685</item>
               <item>496 <hi>Dent</hi>'s <hi>(Arth.)</hi> plain Mans Path-way to Heaven 1682</item>
               <item>497 Dialogue between a Paſtor and Pariſhioners, touching the Lords Supper 1684</item>
               <item>498 <hi>Dyer</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Works in divers Sermons of Chriſts Famous Titles, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>499 Biſhop <hi>Duppa</hi>'s Holy Rules and helps to Devotions, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1683</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:46599:9"/>
               <item>500 Enter into thy Cloſet: Or Method for private Devotion, 5th Edit. <hi>London</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>501 <hi>Flavel</hi>'s <hi>(J.)</hi> Saint indeed: Or great Work of a Chriſtian opened, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>502 — Preparation for ſufferings, or beſt Work in the worſt Times 1683</item>
               <item>503 — Token for Mourners, or Advice of Chriſt to a diſtreſſed Mother 1680</item>
               <item>504 Fire out of Water, in a Sermon at <hi>Tunbridge,</hi> with Meditation upon Waters, by Dr. <hi>Walker</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>505 Gods Voice againſt Pride, in Dreſs and Apparel, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>506 Great Evil of Health-drinking, with Remedies and Antidotes againſt it 1684</item>
               <item>507 <hi>Gouge (Th.)</hi> God's call to <hi>England</hi> for Thankfulneſs after great Deliverances 1680</item>
               <item>508 <hi>Goodwin (J.)</hi> Saints Intereſt in God, in ſeveral Sermons, on 5th of <hi>November</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>509 Golden Chain to link the penitent Sinner unto God, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>R. B.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>510 <hi>Gearing (W.)</hi> Sacred Diary, or ſelect Meditations, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>511 <hi>Griffith</hi>'s plain Diſcourſe on the Lords Supper 1684</item>
               <item>512 <hi>Grotius (H.)</hi> his moſt choice Diſcourſes of God and his Providence, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>513 <hi>Gerard</hi>'s Meditations and Prayers, Engliſhed by <hi>R. Winterton</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>514 <hi>Herbert (Geo.)</hi> ſacred Poems, and pivate Ejaculations, 8th. Edition 1660</item>
               <item>515 <hi>Harwood</hi>'s <hi>(James)</hi> paſſing-Bell Rung out 1657</item>
               <item>516 Hiſtory of the Sufferings of Chriſt, with the ſayings of Eminent Divines 1684</item>
               <item>517 <hi>How (J.)</hi> Self-dedication diſcourſed, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> for a great Deliverance 1682</item>
               <item>518 <hi>Horneck</hi>'s (Dr) Exerciſe of prayer, or a help to Devotion 1685</item>
               <item>519 <hi>Herle</hi>'s <hi>(Ch.)</hi> 3. Treatiſes of worldly Policy, Moral prudence and Chriſtian Wiſdom 1670</item>
               <item>520 <hi>Hall</hi>'s (Bp. <hi>Joſ.</hi>) Great Myſtery of Godlineſs, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>521 Hiſtory o<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> Jeſus Chriſt, digeſted into devotional Meditions 1685</item>
               <item>522 — Of the ſufferings of Chriſt, with the ſayings of Eminent Divines 1684</item>
               <item>523 <hi>Jaco<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>s</hi> Ladder, or a Manual of Devotions, by <hi>J. Hall,</hi> B. D. 1682</item>
               <item>524 Love of Jeſus, or Meditations and Directions for to Love Jeſus unto Death 1678</item>
               <item>525 Ladies Calling, by the Author of the whole Duty of Man <hi>Ox.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>526 <hi>Laud</hi>'s (Archbp.) Daily Exerciſe of a Chriſtian, or holy Devotions 1683</item>
               <item>527 <hi>Lowth</hi>'s <hi>(Sim.)</hi> Catechetical Queſtions, conformed to the Doctrine of the Church of <hi>England</hi>
               </item>
               <item>528 <hi>Lovel</hi>'s <hi>(A.)</hi> practical Rule of Chriſtian piety 1685</item>
               <item>529 Mirror of Martyrs, with their prayers and preparations for their laſt farewel 1685</item>
               <item>530 Method and Order for private Devotion, by Bp. <hi>VVhetenhal,</hi> 5th Edition 1684</item>
               <item>531 Mothers Bleſſing, or Godly counſel of a Gentlewoman to her Children 1674</item>
               <item>532 Mercy of having godly Parents, with the duties of Children that have ſuch 1668</item>
               <item>533 <hi>Mancheſter Al M<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ndo,</hi> or Lord <hi>Mancheſters</hi> Contemplations of Death <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1667</item>
               <item>534 <hi>Martindale</hi>'s <hi>(A.)</hi> Guide for young Chriſtians in the way to ſalvation 1682</item>
               <item>535 <hi>Moulin</hi>'s <hi>(Pet. Du.)</hi> Week of Soliloquies and Prayers, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>536 Method to reduce Romaniſts from Popery to Proteſtancy 1682</item>
               <item>537 New-years-gift compoſed of Prayers and Meditations, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>538 Pilgrims guide from the Cradle to his Death-bed (with Copper cuts) 1684</item>
               <item>539 <hi>Pemble</hi>'s <hi>(W.)</hi> Introduction to the worthy Receiving the Sacrament 1635</item>
               <item>540 Proteſtant Prayer-book, againſt the Erroneous Doctrine of the Papiſts, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>541 Practice of Piety, directing a Chriſtian how to walk, in 12<hi>o.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>542 —Idem in 24. Amplified by the Author 1675</item>
               <item>543 Private Devotions digeſted into ſix Letanies, by <hi>H. Valentine</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>544 —Idem, with Directions and Prayers for the Lords day, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> Ibid.</item>
               <item>545 <hi>Pelling</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Collections of prayers, with a particular Office for Sacrament-days</item>
               <item>546 Preparations to a holy Life, or Devotions for Families and private Perſons 1684</item>
               <pb n="7" facs="tcp:46599:9"/>
               <item>547 Private Pſalter, or Manual of Devotion <hi>London</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>548 Paſtor and his Pariſhioners, A Dialogue between them, about the Lords Supper 1684</item>
               <item>549 <hi>Patrick</hi>'s <hi>(Sim.)</hi> Hearts eaſe, or a Remedy againſt all Troubles 1682</item>
               <item>550 <hi>Pool</hi>'s <hi>(M.)</hi> Dialogue between a Popiſh prieſt and an <hi>Engliſh</hi> Proteſtant 1685</item>
               <item>551 Penitent Lady, or Reflect. on the Mercy of God, by Madam <hi>La Valliere</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>552 Poſy of godly Prayers, fit for every Chriſtian to uſe 1683</item>
               <item>553 <hi>Pagit</hi>'s <hi>(Euſebius)</hi> his Hiſtory of the Bible, by Queſtion and Anſwer 1682</item>
               <item>554 <hi>Pink</hi>'s <hi>(VV.)</hi> Tryal of a Chriſtians ſincere Love to Chriſt 1659</item>
               <item>555 Practical Rule of Chriſtian piety, by <hi>B. Arias Montanus</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>556 Reformed Monaſtery: Or the Love of Jeſus, 2d Edition 1678</item>
               <item>557 <hi>Ryther</hi>'s <hi>(J.)</hi> Hue and Cry of Conſcience, after ſecure Sinners 1680</item>
               <item>558 Service or Common-prayer-book, in 12<hi>o,</hi> with ſinging Pſalms <hi>Oxford</hi>
               </item>
               <item>559 —Another in 24<hi>o,</hi> with New Teſtament and Pſalms <hi>London</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>560 <hi>Spurſtow</hi>'s ſix Decads of divine Meditations, on ſeveral Subjects 1668</item>
               <item>561 Safety in a Tempeſt: Or the way to comfort in ſuffering Times 1684</item>
               <item>562 <hi>Scortreth</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Warning-piece for the ſlumbring Virgins 1672</item>
               <item>563 <hi>Selle<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>'s <hi>(A.)</hi> Devout Communicant, with Rules for the Worthy Receiving the Sacrament 1686</item>
               <item>564. Souls Communion with her Saviour, or Hiſtory of Jeſus Chriſt 1685</item>
               <item>565 <hi>Scrivener (Matth.)</hi> his Treatiſe againſt Drunkenneſs, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>566 <hi>Smith</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.) Davids</hi> bleſſed man, or <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>x<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>oſition on the firſt Pſalm 1682</item>
               <item>567 <hi>Strong</hi>'s <hi>(V<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>.)</hi> Heavenly Treaſure, or mans chief good 1656</item>
               <item>568 —Hell Torments in the certain<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>y and eternity of them 1672</item>
               <item>569 School of the Heart in 47. Emblems, Engraven upon copper 1675</item>
               <item>570 —Of Wiſdom, or the Precepts of Chriſtian Morals 1664</item>
               <item>571 <hi>Symonds (Joſ.)</hi> Caſe and cure of a deſerted Soul 1641</item>
               <item>572 <hi>Stubbe</hi>'s <hi>(H)</hi> Happy effects of keeping a good conſc ence 1684</item>
               <item>573 <hi>Su<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>on</hi>'s <hi>(Chr.)</hi> Godly Meditations upon the Holy Sacraments 1683</item>
               <item>574 <hi>Taylor</hi> (Dr. <hi>Jer.</hi>) Rule and Exerc<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>es <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap> living and dying 1660-58</item>
               <item>575 —Golden Grove, or guide to <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap> with Feſtival Hymns, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>576 —Diſcourſe of the Nature, Offi<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>s and Meaſures of Friendſhip 1671</item>
               <item>577 <hi>Vincent (Tho.)</hi> True Chriſt<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ans love of the un<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>e<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>n <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>hr<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ſt 1677</item>
               <item>578 <hi>Valentine</hi>'s <hi>(H.)</hi> private Devotions, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 23 Edition 1684</item>
               <item>579 <hi>Whetenhall</hi>'s (Bp.) Method for private De<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="3 letters">
                     <desc>•••</desc>
                  </gap>ion 1684</item>
               <item>580 —Idem, with an Appendix about <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>equent and holy uſe of the Lords Supper Ibid.</item>
               <item>581 <hi>VValker</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Ant.</hi>) Sermon at <hi>Tunbridge,</hi> and <hi>Bellarmine</hi>'s Meditation on Fountains, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>582 <hi>VVhately (VV.)</hi> Redemption of Time, in a Sermon 1673</item>
               <item>583 Way to comfort in ſuffering Times 1684</item>
               <item>584 <hi>VVatſon</hi>'s <hi>(Th.)</hi> Art of Divine contentment 1682</item>
               <item>585 Whip for the Devil: Or the <hi>R<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>man</hi> conjurer 1682</item>
               <item>586 <hi>VVinſtanley</hi>'s Meditation on the Miſeries of Mans Life and Death</item>
               <item>587 Young mans duty. A diſcourſe about Neceſſity of ſeeking the Lord</item>
               <item>588 Bible with Common prayer and ſinging Pſalms (Turky and Gilt) 12<hi>o London</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>589 Book of Common prayer, with ſinging Pſalms, in 12<hi>o.</hi> Turky Gilt) <hi>London</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>590 —Another in 24<hi>o.</hi> with New Te<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>tament, ſinging Pſalms <hi>London</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>591 —Same again, gilt and filleted Ibid.</item>
               <item>592 —Same again, in Turky Leather and Gilt Ibid.</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:46599:10"/>
               <item>593 Houſe of weeping, or mans laſt progreſs to his laſt home <hi>Lond.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>594 <hi>Drexelius</hi> his conſiderations upon Eternity (with copper cuts) 1684</item>
               <item>595 Self dedication diſcourſed, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> for a great deliverance, by <hi>J. H.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>596 Mothers Bleſſing, or godly counſel of a gentlewoman, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>597 Mercy of having godly parents, and the duties of children, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>598 Proteſtant prayer-book, with a proteſtant Catechiſm, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>599 Practice of Piety, in 24<hi>s</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>600 Willingneſs of Chriſt to ſave ſinners in 3 Divine Dialogues 1675</item>
               <item>601 Daily Excerciſe of a Devout Chriſtian, or Preparat. to Devotion 1683</item>
               <item>602 Private Devotions. <hi>&amp;c.</hi> By <hi>Hen. Valentine</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>603 <hi>Whateley's (W.)</hi> Redemption of time, in a Sermon 1673</item>
               <item>604 Penitent Lady: Or Madam <hi>La Valliere's</hi> Reflections on Gods Mercy 1685</item>
               <item>605 A Week of Soliloquies and Prayers, by <hi>P. Du-Moulin</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>606 A golden Chain to link the penitent ſinner unto God, by <hi>R B.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>607 Way to Heaven, both in <hi>French</hi> and Engliſh, by <hi>Pet. Berault</hi> 1681</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="list">
            <head>Miſcellanies in <hi>Folio,</hi> viz. Hiſtory, Voyages, Plays, Romances, Military, Law, Heraldry, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
            </head>
            <list>
               <item>608 ANnals of King <hi>James</hi> and King <hi>Charles</hi> the Firſt, by Dr. <hi>Frankland</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>609 <hi>Aphoriſms</hi> Civil and Military, out of <hi>Guicciardin, &amp;c.</hi> by <hi>R. Dallington</hi> 1613</item>
               <item>610 <hi>Boccalin</hi>'s Advertiſements from <hi>Parnaſſus,</hi> with the Politick Touchſtone 1674</item>
               <item>611 <hi>Beaumont</hi> and <hi>Fletcher</hi>'s 50 Comedies and Tragedies (laſt Edition) 1676</item>
               <item>612 <hi>Beaumont</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Joſ.) Pſyche,</hi> or Loves Myſtery, in XX <hi>Canto's</hi> 1648</item>
               <item>636 <hi>Bowman</hi>'s <hi>(H.)</hi> Songs for 1. 2, and 3 Voices, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> with Muſical Notes (cut in Cop.) 1679</item>
               <item>614 <hi>Brown</hi> (Dr. <hi>Tho.</hi>) his Enquiries into vulgar and common errors 1650</item>
               <item>615 <hi>Brown</hi> (Dr. <hi>Edw.</hi>) his Travels into divers parts of <hi>Europe</hi> (with Fig.) 1685</item>
               <item>616 <hi>Baker</hi>'s (Sir. <hi>Rich.</hi>) Chronicle of the Kings of <hi>England,</hi> 4th Edit. 1665</item>
               <item>617 <hi>Bacon</hi>'s (Lord <hi>Fr.) Sylva ſylvarum</hi> or natural Hiſtory, with the new <hi>Atlanta's</hi> 1639</item>
               <item>618 —Hiſtory of the Reign of King <hi>Henry</hi> the VIIth. 1662</item>
               <item>619 <hi>Burton</hi>'s Anatomy of Melancholy, what it is, Cauſes and Cures 1660</item>
               <item>620 <hi>Burnet</hi>'s <hi>(Gilb.)</hi> Hiſtory of the Reformation of the Ch. of <hi>Eng.</hi> in 2 Vol.— 1681 —83</item>
               <item>621 <hi>Curia Politiae,</hi> or Apologies of ſeveral Princes, juſtifying to the world their moſt Eminent Actions, (with Eſſigies of Emperors and Kings.) 1673</item>
               <item>622 <hi>Cabala ſive ſcrinia ſacra,</hi> Myſteries of State and Government, in Letters of Il<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>luſtrious Perſons, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> In the Reigns of King <hi>Henry</hi> VIII. Q. <hi>Elizabeth,</hi> K. <hi>Jam.</hi> and King <hi>Charles</hi> 1663</item>
               <item>623 <hi>Cave</hi> (Dr. <hi>Will.</hi>) Lives of the Primitive Fathers, in 2 Vol. (with Braſs Cuts) 1682</item>
               <item>624 <hi>Clark</hi>'s Martyrology of the greateſt Perſecutions and Sufferings in Queen <hi>Mary's</hi> Reign, with the Lives of 32 Famous Engliſh Divines and others (with Copper Cuts) 1677</item>
               <item>625 —Lives of Eminent Perſons in this latter Age, with his own life, (with Copper Cuts) 1683</item>
               <item>626 <hi>Cary</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Rob.</hi>) Chronological Account of Ancient Time 1677</item>
               <item>627 <hi>Caſſandra,</hi> the fam'd Romance, Engliſh'd by Sir <hi>Charles Cotterel</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>628 <hi>Cawley (W.)</hi> Laws of Queen <hi>Elizabeth,</hi> King <hi>James,</hi> and King <hi>Charles,</hi> againſt Jeſuits, Seminary Prieſts, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>629 <hi>Cowley</hi> (Mr. <hi>Abrah.</hi>) his Works in Poetry, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> with the Authors life 1681</item>
               <item>630 <hi>Davenant</hi>'s works, <hi>viz. Gondibert,</hi> a Poem, divers plays, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>631 Deſcription and Maps of Great <hi>Brittain,</hi> and of forreign parts, by <hi>J Speed,</hi> 1674</item>
               <pb n="8" facs="tcp:46599:10"/>
               <item>632 <hi>Dugdale</hi> (Sir <hi>VVill.</hi>) his view of the late Troubles in <hi>England, Lond.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>633 —Summons of the Nobility to great Councils and Parliaments of <hi>England</hi> from <hi>Henry</hi> III. 1685</item>
               <item>634 <hi>Daniel</hi>'s <hi>(S.)</hi> Hiſtory of <hi>England,</hi> with the continuation of <hi>John Truſſell</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>635 Diſp<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ay of Heraldry, with Explanation of the terms of Hawking and Hunting, by <hi>Guillim</hi> 1638</item>
               <item>636 <hi>Don Quixot,</hi> the witty and valourous <hi>Spaniard,</hi> Hiſtory of his Life 1675</item>
               <item>637 <hi>Felthams (Owen)</hi> Reſolves, Divine, Moral, and Political (beſt Edit.) 1677</item>
               <item>638 <hi>Gr<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>tius (Hugo)</hi> Of the Rights of war and peace, with Annotations (laſt Edit.) 1682</item>
               <item>639 <hi>Godfrey</hi> of <hi>Boul<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>gne,</hi> or the recovery of <hi>Jeruſalem</hi> (Heroick poem) 1624</item>
               <item>640 <hi>Guzman de Alfarache,</hi> or the life of the <hi>Spaniſh</hi> Rogue 1623</item>
               <item>641 <hi>Hall (John)</hi> Of Government and Obedience by Scripture and Reaſon 1654</item>
               <item>642 <hi>Howel</hi>'s <hi>(James)</hi> German Diet, or the ballance of <hi>Europe</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>643 Letters and Poems of eminent perſons, in Honour of the Lady of <hi>Newcaſtle</hi> 1686</item>
               <item>644 <hi>Leybourn</hi>'s <hi>(Wil.)</hi> Art of Dyalling, Illuſtrated with ſculptures, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>645 <hi>Mille</hi>'s <hi>(Th.)</hi> Catal. of Honour, or Treaſury of true Nobil. (with Coats of Ar.) 1610</item>
               <item>646 <hi>Nalſon</hi>'s <hi>(J.)</hi> Account of the Journal, <hi>&amp;c</hi> for Tryal of K. <hi>Charles</hi> the Firſt 1684</item>
               <item>647 <hi>Plutarch</hi>'s Lives and Morals, in 2 Vol. (beſt Edition) 1657-76</item>
               <item>648 <hi>Peel</hi>'s Accompts of Debitor and Creditor, with <hi>J. Carpenter</hi>'s Accompts, 2 Vol. 1567</item>
               <item>649 <hi>Raſtal</hi>'s <hi>(William)</hi> Collection of Statutes, continued from <hi>Magna Charta</hi> 1598</item>
               <item>650 <hi>Sandy</hi>'s <hi>(G.)</hi> Tranſlation of <hi>Ovid</hi>'s <hi>Metamorphoſis</hi> (with Annotat. and Fig.) 1632</item>
               <item>651 — His Travels into <hi>Turky, Egypt,</hi> holy Land <hi>&amp;c.</hi> (with braſs Cuts) 1615</item>
               <item>652 <hi>Sanders (Richard)</hi> Phyſiognomy, and Chiromancy, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> with the Art of Memory 1671</item>
               <item>653 <hi>Spenſer</hi>'s <hi>(Edm.)</hi> Fairy Queen, the ſhepheards Calender, with other Poems 1617</item>
               <item>654 <hi>Tavernier</hi>'s <hi>(J. Bapt.)</hi> ſix Voyages through <hi>Turky</hi> into <hi>Perſia,</hi> &amp;c. (with Cuts) 1678</item>
               <item>655 <hi>Truſſel</hi> and <hi>Daniel</hi>'s Collection of the Hiſtory of <hi>England</hi> (laſt Edition) 1685</item>
               <item>656 <hi>VVillis</hi> (Dr. <hi>Tho.</hi>) Diſcourſes concerning the ſoul of bruits, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> (with braſs cuts) 1683</item>
               <item>657 World of Wonders, or preparative Treatiſe to the Apology for <hi>Herodotus</hi> 1608</item>
               <item>658 <hi>Grimeſtone</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Imperial Hiſtory from the firſt Foundation of <hi>Rom.</hi> Mon. 1679</item>
               <item>659 — Eſtates, Empires, and Principalities of the world 1615</item>
               <item>660 — Hiſtory of the <hi>Netherlands,</hi> with <hi>VVill. Croſſes</hi> continuation 1627</item>
               <item>661 — General Hiſtory of <hi>France</hi> (Engliſh'd from <hi>J. de S<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>rres</hi>) 1607</item>
               <item>662 Hiſtory of the VVorld, or an account of Time by <hi>Dyonyſ. Petavius</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>663 — Of the world, or Coſmography, by Dr. <hi>Peter H<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ylin</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>664 — Of the world, or Natural Hiſtory of <hi>C. <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>linius,</hi> Engliſhed by <hi>P. Holland</hi> 1601</item>
               <item>N 1 — Of the world, or Coſmog. and Geog by <hi>Var<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>mus</hi> and <hi>Sanſon,</hi> with Maps 1683</item>
               <item>2 — Of the world, by Sir <hi>VValter Rawleigh,</hi> (firſt and beſt Edit. with Maps) 1614</item>
               <item>3 — Of the world by <hi>Alex. Roſs,</hi> (being a continuation of Sir <hi>VV. Rawleigh</hi>) 1652</item>
               <item>4 — Of the <hi>Punick, Syrian, Parthian, Illyrian, Spaniſh, Hanniballick,</hi> and Roman VVars, by <hi>Appian</hi> of <hi>Al<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>xandria</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>5 — Of the <hi>Romans</hi> by <hi>Titus Livius,</hi> Engliſh'd by <hi>P. Holland</hi> 1600</item>
               <item>6 — Of the <hi>Romans,</hi> of the manner of their encamping, by <hi>Polybius</hi> 1634</item>
               <item>7 — Of the ſtate of <hi>Venice,</hi> by <hi>Mons de Fougales,</hi> Engliſhed by <hi>VV. Shute</hi> 1612</item>
               <item>8 — Of the Signory of <hi>Venice,</hi> by <hi>James H<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>wel,</hi> with political Reflections 1663</item>
               <item>9 — Of the wars of <hi>Italy</hi> and other parts, by <hi>Fr. Guicciardin</hi> 1599</item>
               <item>10 —Of <hi>Europe,</hi> more particularly the Republick of <hi>V<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>nice,</hi> by <hi>Bapt. Nani</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>11 — Of the wars of <hi>Italy,</hi> &amp;c. by <hi>P. Geo. Capriata,</hi> engliſhed by <hi>Monmouth</hi> 1663</item>
               <item>11 — Of <hi>Italy</hi> in its Original, Glory, Ruin, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>Edm. VVarcup</hi> 1665</item>
               <item>12 —Of <hi>Flore<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>,</hi> by <hi>Nic. Machiavil,</hi> with the reſt of his works 1683</item>
               <item>13 — Of <hi>Germ<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ny,</hi> with the Annals and Deſc. by <hi>C. Ta<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>itus,</hi> with Sir <hi>H. Savils</hi> Notes</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:46599:11"/>
               <item>14 —Of the Civil Wars of <hi>France,</hi> by <hi>C. Davila Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>15 —Of the Life of the D. of <hi>Eſpernon</hi> being a continuation of <hi>Davila</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>16 —Of the Battels for 60 years in <hi>France,</hi> by way of Commentary, by <hi>Montluc</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>17 —Of <hi>Joſephus,</hi> being the Antiquities and Wars of the <hi>Jews,</hi> with the Embaſſy of <hi>Philo Judaeus</hi> to <hi>Caius Caligula,</hi> (beſt Edition with Cuts) 1683</item>
               <item>18 —Of the <hi>Athenian</hi> Wars, by <hi>Thucydides. Engliſhed</hi> by <hi>T. Nicolls</hi> 1553</item>
               <item>19 —Of the <hi>Turks,</hi> with the Lives of the <hi>Ottoman</hi> Kings, by <hi>F. Knolles</hi> (with Fig.) 1631</item>
               <item>20 —Of the <hi>Turkiſh</hi> Empire, from 1623 to 1677, by <hi>P. Rycaut</hi> (with cuts) 1680</item>
               <item>21 —Of <hi>Paleſtine</hi> and Confines thereof, by <hi>Th. Fuller</hi> (with Maps) 1650</item>
               <item>22 —Of Ancient time, or Chronological account thereof, by <hi>R. Cary</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>23 —Chronicle, Or<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>er and Harmony of the Old and New Teſtament, with many other Learned Treatiſes, by Dr. <hi>Jn. Lightfoot</hi> (with the Authors Life) 2 Vol. 1684</item>
               <item>24 —Of the Council of <hi>Trent,</hi> by Father <hi>Paul, Engliſhed</hi> by <hi>N. B.</hi> 1629</item>
               <item>25 —Review of the Council of <hi>Trent,</hi> by <hi>G. Lambaine</hi> 1638</item>
               <item>26 —Of Man: or the Wonders of the Little World, by <hi>N. Wanley</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>27 —Of the Cardinals of the <hi>Roman</hi> Church, <hi>Engliſhed</hi> by <hi>G. H</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>28 —Of <hi>Sol<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="4 letters">
                        <desc>••••</desc>
                     </gap>s</hi> Temple Pourtrayed by Scripture Light (with Figures) 1659</item>
               <item>29 —Of the Reformation of the Church of <hi>England,</hi> by <hi>P. Heylin</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>30 —Of the Popes Intollerable Uſurpations upon the Liberties of the Kings and Subjects of <hi>England,</hi> &amp;c by <hi>VV. P.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>31 —Of <hi>Englend,</hi> by <hi>S. Daniel</hi> with <hi>J. Truſſell's</hi> continuation 1685</item>
               <item>32 —Of <hi>England</hi> with a Gloſſary, by Dr. <hi>Rob. Brady</hi> in 2 Vol. 1684</item>
               <item>33 —Of the Execrable <hi>Iriſh</hi> Rebellion, with a reflection on the ſtate 1680</item>
               <item>34 —Of all the ſummons of the Nobility of <hi>England</hi> to the great Councils and Parliaments thereof, from 49th of K. <hi>Hen.</hi> 3d. by Sir <hi>VV. Dugdale</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>35 —<hi>Camden's Britannia:</hi> or deſcription of <hi>England</hi> &amp;c. with Maps (beſt Edition) 1637</item>
               <item>36 —A <hi>Samme's Britannia:</hi> or Antiquities of Ancient <hi>Britain</hi> (with Fig.) 1676</item>
               <item>37 —<hi>Engliſh</hi> Janus and <hi>Englands</hi> Epinomi of the Rites and Cuſtoms of the Anci<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ent <hi>Britans,</hi> by <hi>Jn. Selden,</hi> with large Notes of Dr. <hi>Littleton</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>38 —And Deſcription of the County of <hi>Kent,</hi> being an exact ſurvey thereof, by <hi>J. Philpot</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>39 —Of the Church of <hi>Scotland</hi> from 203 to the end of K. <hi>James</hi> VI Reign, by <hi>Spotſwood</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>40 —Of the Church, by <hi>Euſebius,</hi> &amp;c. with the Life of <hi>Conſtantine</hi> 1636</item>
               <item>41 —Of the Church ſince the days of our Saviour, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>Pat. Sypmſ n</hi> 1634</item>
               <item>42 —<hi>R. Broughton</hi>'s Eccleſiaſtical Hiſtory of Great <hi>Brittaine</hi> 1633</item>
               <item>43 —Of this Iron Age: of the ſtate of <hi>Europe</hi> as in the year 1500 of the Original and cauſes of all the Wars <hi>&amp;c.</hi> to 1659 (with Lively Effigies of great per.) 1659</item>
               <item>44 —Of Four-Footed Beaſts and Serpents, by <hi>C. Geſner</hi> &amp;c. (beſt Edition) 1658</item>
               <item>45 —Of the Wars of the Emperou<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> 
                  <hi>Juſtinian,</hi> by <hi>Pr<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>copius, Engliſhed</hi> by <hi>H. H.</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>46 —Of the Iſland of <hi>Barbad<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>es,</hi> by <hi>R. Ligen</hi> (with copper cuts) 1673</item>
               <item>47 —Of Voyages unto the <hi>Eaſt</hi> and <hi>VVeſt Endies</hi> (with Maps) by <hi>V. Linſchoten</hi>
               </item>
               <item>48 —<hi>Africa:</hi> being an Accurate deſcription of <hi>Egypt, Barbary, Lybia,</hi> and <hi>Bel<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ledulgerid,</hi> by <hi>J. Ogilby</hi> (with curious Sculptures) 1670</item>
               <item>49 —<hi>Britannia:</hi> or an Illuſtration of <hi>England,</hi> and deſcription of the principal Roads thereof, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>J. Ogilby</hi> (with curious Sculptures) 1675</item>
               <item>50 —Entertainment of K. <hi>Charles</hi> 2d in his paſſage through the City of <hi>London</hi> to his Coronation (w<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>h Sculptures) by <hi>J. Ogilby</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>51 —Of the <hi>Tr<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>j<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>n</hi> Wars <hi>&amp;c.</hi> deſcribed by <hi>Homer,</hi> Adorn'd with Sculptures, and Illu<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>t<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>ted wi<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>h Annotat. by <hi>J. Ogilby,</hi> in 2 Vol.</item>
               <pb n="9" facs="tcp:46599:11"/>
               <item>52 —of the Wars of <hi>Flanders,</hi> by Cardinal <hi>Bentivoglio,</hi> with Sculptures 1654</item>
               <item>53 —of the United Provinces of <hi>Flanders,</hi> by Card. <hi>Bentivoglio</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>54 —of the Low-Country Wars, by <hi>Fam. Strada,</hi> with Cuts 1650</item>
               <item>55 —of <hi>Spain,</hi> by <hi>Lewis de Mayerne,</hi> Engliſhed by <hi>Edw. Grimeſtone</hi> 1612</item>
               <item>56 —of the Uniting the Kingdom of <hi>Portugal</hi> to the Crown of <hi>Caſtile</hi> 1600</item>
               <item>57 —of the Lives of the Kings of <hi>England,</hi> by Sir <hi>Winſton Churchil</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>58 —of the Kings of <hi>England,</hi> by way of Chronicle, by Sir <hi>Rich. Baker</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>59 —of <hi>England, Scotland</hi> and <hi>Ireland,</hi> by <hi>Ralph Hellingſhed,</hi> 2 Volumes</item>
               <item>60 —of the Kings of <hi>England,</hi> with their Coats of Arms, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>Franc. Sandford</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>61 —of the Nobility and Gentry of <hi>England,</hi> or diſplay of Heraldry, by <hi>Guillim</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>62 —of <hi>Great Brittain,</hi> deſcribed in curious Maps. by <hi>Jc. Speed</hi> 1634</item>
               <item>Together with his Chronicle, both in Royal paper, 2 Vol. 1675</item>
               <item>63 —of the affairs of <hi>G. Brit.</hi> and <hi>Irel.</hi> from the beg of <hi>Ch.</hi> 1ſt to K. <hi>Ch.</hi> 2d, by <hi>Whitlock</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>64 —of the Baronage or Nobility of <hi>England,</hi> in 2 parts, by Sir <hi>Will. Dugdale</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>65 —of the Antiquities of <hi>Warwickſhire,</hi> illuſtrated with Figures, by Sir <hi>W. Dugdale</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>66 —of St. <hi>Pauls</hi> Cathedral in <hi>London,</hi> by Sir <hi>W. Dugdale</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>67 —of the Church of <hi>Great Brittain,</hi> by <hi>Ser. Croſſy</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>68 —of the Church of <hi>G. Brittain</hi> from Chriſt's time to 1648. by <hi>Tho. Fuller</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>69 —of the Church of <hi>Scotland</hi> from the beginning of the Reform. by <hi>D. Calderwood</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>70 —of the Catholick Church from 600 to 1600. by <hi>Alex. Petrie Hague</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>71 —of the Reformation of the Church of <hi>England,</hi> by <hi>G. Burnet,</hi> 2 Vol. (cuts) 1681</item>
               <item>72 —of the Beginnings and progreſs of the <hi>Presbyterians,</hi> by <hi>P. Heylin</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>73 —of the Plots of the <hi>Presbyterians,</hi> by <hi>Henry Foulis</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>74 —of <hi>Romiſh</hi> Treaſons, Conſpiracies, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>Henry Fowlis</hi>
               </item>
               <item>75 —of <hi>Edward</hi> the 4th, by <hi>Will Habbington</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>76 —of the Life and Reign of King <hi>Richard</hi> the 3d, by <hi>G. Buck</hi> 1647</item>
               <item>77 —of the Reign of <hi>Henry</hi> the 7th, by the Lord <hi>Bacon</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>77 —of <hi>Henry</hi> 8th, <hi>Edward</hi> 6th, and Q. <hi>Mary,</hi> by Bp. <hi>Godwin</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>* —of the Reign of King <hi>Henry</hi> the 8th, by L. <hi>Herb<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>rt</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>78 —of Queen <hi>Elizabeth,</hi> with a Table, by <hi>W. Cambden</hi>
               </item>
               <item>79 —of the Life and Reign of King <hi>James,</hi> by <hi>Arthur Wilſon</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>80 —of King <hi>James</hi> and King <hi>Charles</hi> the firſt, by Dr. <hi>Frankland</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>81 —of the Reign of King <hi>Charles</hi> the firſt, by <hi>Ham. L'Eſtrange</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>82 —of the Reigns of <hi>Mary</hi> Q. of <hi>Scots,</hi> and King <hi>James,</hi> by <hi>Sanderſon</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>83 —of the Action and Succeſſes of the Army under <hi>Fairfax,</hi> by <hi>Sprigg</hi> 1647</item>
               <item>84 —of the late Troubles in <hi>England,</hi> by Sir <hi>W. Dugdale</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>85 —of the Parliament of <hi>England,</hi> by <hi>Tho May</hi> 1647</item>
               <item>86 —of the Civil Wars between <hi>Lancaster</hi> and <hi>York,</hi> by <hi>Blondi</hi> 1641</item>
               <item>87 —of all Queen <hi>Elizabeths</hi> Parliaments, by Sir <hi>Sim. D' Ewes</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>88 —of <hi>Eng.</hi> and <hi>Scotl.</hi> by way of Memoirs, in the time of Q. <hi>Eliz.</hi> by Sir <hi>J. Melvin</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>89 —of the Tumults in <hi>Scotland,</hi> by King <hi>Charles</hi> the firſt 163</item>
               <item>90 —of the Funeral Monuments in <hi>Eng.</hi> with the Fall of Monaſteries, by <hi>Weaver</hi> 1631</item>
               <item>91 —of Affairs &amp; priv. paſſ. of State, with the E. of <hi>Straff.</hi> Tr. by <hi>J. Ruſhworth,</hi> in 4 Vol. 1680</item>
               <item>92 — of Affairs and paſſages of State, collected by Dr. <hi>J. Nalſon,</hi> 2 Vol. 1682</item>
               <item>93 —of the Antiquities of <hi>Rutland,</hi> by <hi>Jo. Weight,</hi> with Sculptures 1684</item>
               <item>94 —of the Antiquities of <hi>Nottinghamſhire,</hi> by <hi>Rob. Thoroton</hi> (with cuts) 1677</item>
               <item>95 —of the Antiquities of <hi>Leicesterſhire,</hi> by <hi>Will. Burton</hi>
               </item>
               <item>96 —of <hi>Great Brittain,</hi> eſpecially <hi>Cheſhire,</hi> by <hi>Pet. Leicester</hi>
               </item>
               <item>97 —of <hi>Antoninus</hi> his Itinerary through <hi>Brittain,</hi> with <hi>Burton</hi>'s Commentary 1658</item>
               <item>98 —and Deſcript. of the County <hi>Palatine</hi> of <hi>Chester,</hi> by <hi>D. King</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>99 —of <hi>London,</hi> Survey of its Original, Increaſe, Government, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>John Stow</hi> 1633</item>
               <item>100 —of <hi>Ethiopia,</hi> by <hi>Job Ludolphus</hi> (with curious figures) 1682</item>
               <item>101 —of the Monarchy of <hi>China,</hi> by <hi>Alvarez Samedo</hi> (with figures) 1635</item>
               <pb n="10" facs="tcp:46599:12"/>
               <item>102 —of the Iſland of <hi>Ceylon</hi> in the <hi>Eaſt Indies,</hi> by <hi>R. Knox</hi> (with figures) 1681</item>
               <item>103 —of the Holy State and War, by <hi>Tho. Fuller</hi> 1639</item>
               <item>104 —of the 28 <hi>Caribby</hi> Iſlands; <hi>viz. Barbadoes, Mevis,</hi> St. <hi>C<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>riſtophers,</hi> &amp;c. 1666</item>
               <item>105 —of the <hi>Cruſade,</hi> or the Chriſtians Expedition into the Holy Land 1685</item>
               <item>106 <hi>Heylin</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Peter</hi>) Hiſtorical and Miſcellaneous Tracts 1681</item>
               <item>107 — his <hi>Coſmography,</hi> or Hiſtory of the World, with Maps 1680</item>
               <item>108 <hi>Janus Angl<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>rum,</hi> and Original of Eccleſiaſtical Juriſdictions, by <hi>Jo Selden</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>109 Laws and Acts of Parliament made in <hi>Scotland,</hi> with the <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ffigies of their Kings 1681</item>
               <item>110 <hi>Ludolphus Job</hi>) his Hiſtory of <hi>Ethiopia</hi> (with curious Sculptures) 1682</item>
               <item>111 Lives of the rimitive Fathers, in 2 Volumes by Dr. <hi>W. Cave</hi> (with cuts) 1682</item>
               <item>112 —of the Eminent Perſons of this latter Age. by <hi>Sam C<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>arke</hi> (figures) 1683</item>
               <item>113 —of K <hi>Cha.</hi> 1ſt with the Lives of the Noble Perſons that died for him, by <hi>Lloyd</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>114 —of <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>rchbiſhop <hi>Laud,</hi> by Dr. <hi>Peter Heylin</hi>
               </item>
               <item>115 —of the Philoſophers, in 8 parts, with their Effigies, by <hi>Tho. Stanley</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>116 —of King <hi>L<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>wis</hi> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>he 13th of <hi>France,</hi> and Cardinal <hi>Richelieu</hi> 1646</item>
               <item>117 <hi>Ma<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>h<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>vel</hi>'s (<hi>Nic<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi> Works; <hi>viz.</hi> Hiſtory of <hi>Fl<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>r<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>nce, Prince,</hi> &amp;c 1680</item>
               <item>118 Diſcourſe of Well governing a Kingdom, againſt <hi>Nic. Machiavell</hi> 1608</item>
               <item>119 <hi>Mezeray</hi>'s Hiſtory of <hi>France</hi> from <hi>
                     <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>haramond</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>120 Military Eſſays of the <hi>Graecian</hi> and <hi>Roman</hi> Art of War, by Sir <hi>James Turner</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>121 <hi>Nero Caeſar,</hi> or Monarchy depraved, an Hiſtorical Work 1624</item>
               <item>122 <hi>Nani</hi>'s <hi>(Bapt.)</hi> Hiſtory of <hi>Venice,</hi> with a Diſcourſe of the preſent Affairs of <hi>Europe</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>123 <hi>Ogilby</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Deſcription of <hi>China,</hi> in 2 Volumes, with figures 1673</item>
               <item>124 —his Deſcription of <hi>Japan,</hi> with figures 1670</item>
               <item>125 —his Deſcription of <hi>America</hi> (with curious Sculptures) 1671</item>
               <item>126 —his Deſcription of <hi>Aſia</hi> (with cuts) 1673</item>
               <item>127 <hi>Philli<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>s (Edw.)</hi> New World of Words, or General <hi>Engliſh</hi> Dictionary 1678</item>
               <item>128 <hi>Paulo Peruta</hi>'s Maxims of State 1657</item>
               <item>129 <hi>Mich. de Montaigues</hi> Eſſays, Moral. Politick and M<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>litary 1632</item>
               <item>130 <hi>Ruſhwo th</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Hiſtorical Collections of Affairs of <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>tate, with the Trial of the Earl of <hi>Straff<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>rd,</hi> in 4 Volumes of the large paper gilt and let.
<list>
                     <item>1659.</item>
                     <item>168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                           <desc>•</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </item>
                  </list>
               </item>
               <item>131 <hi>Speed</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Maps and Deſcription of <hi>G. Brittain,</hi> with Forreign Maps 1674</item>
               <item>132 <hi>Jo. Selden</hi>'s Tracts of the Adminiſtration of Inteſtate Goods, <hi>&amp;c. Lond.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>133 <hi>Thucidides</hi> his Hiſtory of the <hi>A<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>h<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>nian</hi> War, Engliſhed by <hi>T. Nicholls</hi> 1550</item>
               <item>134 Treaſury of Ancient and Modern Times, or Hiſtorical Collection, in 2 V<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>l 1613</item>
               <item>135 <hi>Varenius</hi> and <hi>S<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="3 letters">
                        <desc>•••</desc>
                     </gap>on</hi>'s <hi>Coſ<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ography</hi> and <hi>Geography</hi> with 100 Maps and Figures) 1683</item>
               <item>13<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> View f the late Troubles in <hi>England,</hi> by Sir <hi>W. Dugdale</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>* <hi>W<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>n</hi>'s Hiſtory of <hi>Great Brittain.</hi> containing the Life of King <hi>James</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>137 <hi>W<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>t<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>ck</hi>'s <hi>Bulſt.</hi>) Memorials of <hi>Engliſh</hi> Affairs from the beg of <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ſt</hi> to 1660 <hi>Lon</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>138 <hi>W<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>l<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="3 letters">
                        <desc>•••</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>'s <hi>(L<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>)</hi> Perf<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ct S<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ateſman and Object of his Office 1668</item>
               <item>139 Bp. <hi>Wilkins</hi> his Real Character and Philoſophical Language 1658</item>
               <item>140 <hi>Will<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ughby</hi>'s <hi>(Franc.)</hi> Deſcrip of all ſorts of Birds with the Art of Fowling, with figur. 1658</item>
            </list>
            <div type="list">
               <head>Military.</head>
               <list>
                  <item>141 Seige of <hi>Breda,</hi> by <hi>Herman Hugo,</hi> with Copper Plates 1627</item>
                  <item>142 Sir <hi>Jo. Turner</hi>'s Military Eſſays of the <hi>Roman</hi> and <hi>Grecian</hi> Art of War 1683</item>
                  <item>143 Duke of <hi>Albermarle</hi>'s Obſervations on Military and Politick Affairs 1671</item>
                  <item>144 <hi>Markham's (Franc.)</hi> five Decades of Epiſtles of War 1622</item>
                  <item>145 Inſtructions for riding and managing the great Horſe: with curious Fi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gures; by Mounſier <hi>Pluvinell</hi> in <hi>French. Amſt.</hi> 1668</item>
                  <item>146 Art Military, or Inſtructions for Chivalry, by <hi>Cruſo</hi>
                  </item>
               </list>
            </div>
            <div type="list">
               <head>Voyages, Travels, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </head>
               <list>
                  <item>147 <hi>Purchas (Sam.)</hi> his Pilgrims &amp; Pilgrimage; being a Collect. of Navigations, Voyages, Land-Travels, Diſcoveries and Plantations in the ſeveral parts of the World; with an account of their ſeveral Religions, 4 <hi>Vol. Lond.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <pb n="11" facs="tcp:46599:12"/>
                  <item>148 <hi>Hackluyt (Rich.)</hi> his Voyages, Navigations, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 3 parts, 2 Vol. compleat 1600</item>
                  <item>149 <hi>Taverniers (Jo. Bapt.)</hi> Voyages to, and Travels in <hi>Turky, Perſia, Eaſt Indies</hi> 1678</item>
                  <item>150 <hi>Herberts</hi> (Sir <hi>Tho.</hi>) Travels in <hi>Greece, Aegypt, Perſia,</hi> &amp;c. with Sculptures</item>
                  <item>151 <hi>VVheeler</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Journey into <hi>Greece;</hi> illuſtrated with Sculptures 1682</item>
                  <item>152 <hi>Pietro Della Vall's</hi> Travels into <hi>Eaſt-India,</hi> and <hi>Arabia deſerta</hi> 1667</item>
                  <item>153 <hi>Knoxes</hi> Hiſtory of the Iſland of <hi>Ceylon</hi> in the <hi>East Indies</hi> 1681</item>
                  <item>154 Voyages and Travels of Ambaſſadors into <hi>Muſcovy, Tarta y, Perſia,</hi> &amp;c. 1669</item>
                  <item>155 <hi>M<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                           <desc>•</desc>
                        </gap>ryſon's (Fynes)</hi> Thirty Years Travels through <hi>Germany, Italy, Turky,</hi> &amp;c. 1617</item>
                  <item>156 <hi>Hayward (Edw.)</hi> Of the ſizes of riggings for all ſorts of Ships 1655</item>
                  <item>157 <hi>Pin<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                           <desc>•</desc>
                        </gap>o (Ferd. Mend.)</hi> his Travels <hi>Lud.</hi>
                  </item>
               </list>
            </div>
            <div type="list">
               <head>Law.</head>
               <list>
                  <item>158 <hi>Cawley's (Will.)</hi> Explanation of the Laws againſt Recuſants 1680</item>
                  <item>159 <hi>Cowels</hi> Interpreter of Law Terms, with <hi>Manley</hi>'s Appendix 1684</item>
                  <item>160 <hi>Cotton</hi>'s (S<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>r <hi>Robert</hi>) Abridgment of the Records in the Tower 1657</item>
                  <item>161 <hi>Dalton</hi>'s <hi>(Mich.)</hi> practice of Country Juſtices in and out of the Seſſions. 1666</item>
                  <item>162 Laws &amp; Stat. of the Kingd. of <hi>Scot.</hi> with the effig<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap> of their Kings, &amp; Inter of their terms 1661</item>
                  <item>163 Modern Reports of Caſes adjudged under King <hi>Charles</hi> the firſt 1682</item>
                  <item>164 Eccleſiaſtical Juriſdiction of Teſtaments 1683</item>
                  <item>165 <hi>Grotius (Hugo)</hi> Rights of War and Peace 1682</item>
               </list>
            </div>
            <div type="list">
               <head>Heraldry.</head>
               <list>
                  <item>166 <hi>Morgan</hi>'s <hi>(S)</hi> Sphere of the Gentry, with Arms and Blazons; with Figures 1661</item>
                  <item>167 <hi>Guillim</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Diſplay of Herald. with great Enlarg. and many curious Fig. 1679</item>
                  <item>168 <hi>Brook</hi>'s <hi>(Ralph)</hi> catalogue of the Succeſſion of the Kings and Nobility of <hi>Engl.</hi> 1622</item>
                  <item>169 <hi>Selden</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Titles of Honour; with Figures 1612</item>
                  <item>170 <hi>Sandford</hi>'s <hi>(Fr.)</hi> Hiſt. of the Kings and Nobility of <hi>England</hi> with curious Fig. 1683</item>
                  <item>171 Theatre of Honour and Knighthood; or the Original of Monarchies, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1623</item>
                  <item>172 <hi>Sandfords</hi> Ge<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ealogical H ſtory of the King, of <hi>Portugal;</hi> with Figures 1662</item>
                  <item>173 Inſt t of the Laws and Cer. of the Ord. of the Gart. by <hi>Elias Aſhmole;</hi> lar. pap. 1672</item>
                  <item>174 <hi>Y<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                           <desc>•</desc>
                        </gap>rk (James)</hi> U<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ion of Honour. 1641</item>
               </list>
            </div>
         </div>
         <div type="list">
            <head>Miſcellanies; <hi>viz</hi> Hist<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                  <desc>•</desc>
               </gap>ry, Voyages, Travels, Romances, Law, <hi>&amp;c. Quarto.</hi>
            </head>
            <list>
               <item>175 ACcount of the Aſſaults on the <hi>VVeſt-Indies</hi> by the <hi>Bucaniers;</hi> (with F<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>g) <hi>Lond.</hi> 168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>176 Arra<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>gnment of the creature at the Bar of Reaſon and Religion 1031</item>
               <item>177 Lord <hi>B<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>c<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>n</hi>'s Eſſ<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ys; or counſels, civil an<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> Moral</item>
               <item>178 —Advancement of D<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>vine and Humane Learn ng 1605</item>
               <item>179 <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>rlet<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>n (VValt.)</hi> Antiq tities of great <hi>Bri<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>tain;</hi> (with F<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>gures) 1663</item>
               <item>180 <hi>Camd<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>n</hi>'s Remains concerning <hi>Brittain</hi> 1623</item>
               <item>181 <hi>Clavel (Rog.)</hi> Tables for forbearance, and Di<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>compt of Money 1683</item>
               <item>18<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> Come<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>t<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ries o<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> the Civil Wars of <hi>F<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ance,</hi> by <hi>Tho T<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>mme</hi> 1574</item>
               <item>183 Certain <hi>M ſc llany</hi> Works of the Lord <hi>Ba<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="3 letters">
                        <desc>•••</desc>
                     </gap>;</hi> publ ſhed by Dr. <hi>R<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>w<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>igh</hi> 1629</item>
               <item>184 <hi>Clauds</hi> Hiſtorical De<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ence of the Reformation 1683</item>
               <item>185 Lord <hi>C<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>rend n</hi>'s Survey of <hi>H<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>bb<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>'s Leviathan: large Paper <hi>Oxon</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>186 <hi>Feltham (Owen)</hi> Reſolves, Divine, Moral, and Political <hi>Lond.</hi> 1618</item>
               <item>187 <hi>Goodwin (Fran.)</hi> Catalogue of the Biſhops of <hi>England</hi> 1615</item>
               <item>188 <hi>H<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ylin (Pet.)</hi> Geogra<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>hy; or Deſcription of the World 1636</item>
               <item>189 <hi>Huart (John)</hi> Tryal of Wits 1594</item>
               <item>190 Hiſtory and Annals of the Reign of Queen <hi>Elizabeth</hi> 1625</item>
               <item>191 — of Saint <hi>George</hi> of <hi>Cappadocia</hi> by <hi>Pet<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>r H<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ylyn</hi> 1633</item>
               <item>192 —of the Gunpowder Treaſon 1681</item>
               <item>193 —of <hi>Gavelkind,</hi> with the Etymology thereof, by <hi>S. Taylor</hi> 1663</item>
               <item>194 <hi>Lloyd (Lod.)</hi> Stratage<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>s of <hi>Jeru<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>alem,</hi> and Martial Laws of the <hi>Jews</hi> 1602</item>
               <item>195 <hi>London (VVill.)</hi> Catalogue of the moſt vendible Books in <hi>England</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>196 Politick and Military Diſcourſes of the Lord <hi>de la Nove,</hi> wanting the Title</item>
               <item>197 <hi>Rous (Francis) Archiologiae Artic<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>:</hi> or Greek Antiquities 1685</item>
               <pb n="12" facs="tcp:46599:13"/>
               <item>198 Relations of the moſt famous Kingdoms and Common-Wealths in the World 1616</item>
               <item>199 <hi>Swan (John) Redde debitum</hi> or Defence of the Three chief Fatherhoods 1640</item>
               <item>200 <hi>Sw<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>diſh</hi> Intelligence from the Kings incamping before <hi>Norimberg</hi> to his Death 1633</item>
               <item>201 <hi>Speculum Belli Sacri,</hi> or the Looking glaſs of the holy War 1624</item>
               <item>202 <hi>S<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>monds (Ed.)</hi> Vindic of King <hi>Charles,</hi> with a Parallel betw. his ſuffer and our Savi. 1648</item>
               <item>203 <hi>S<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ru<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Voyages and Travels through <hi>Greece, Moſcovy,</hi> &amp;c. (with fig.) <hi>Lond.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>204 <hi>Selden (J.)</hi> his Hiſtory of Tythes 1678</item>
               <item>205 <hi>Swan (John)</hi> of the manner how, and time when the World ſhall end 1643</item>
               <item>206 <hi>Swin<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>u<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>e (VVill.)</hi> Treatiſe of Teſtaments and Laſt Wills 1677</item>
               <item>207 The Hiſtory of the Sabbath in 2 Books, by <hi>Peter Heylin</hi> 1636</item>
               <item>208 Travels of the Patriarchs, Prophets, our Saviour Chriſt, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>209 <hi>Taylor (Silas)</hi> Hiſtory and Etymology of <hi>Gavelkind</hi> 1663</item>
               <item>210 <hi>VViſeman (Rob.)</hi> Excellency of the Civil Law above other Laws 1657</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="list">
            <head>Miſcellanies, Hiſtories, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> in Octavo.</head>
            <list>
               <item>211 Animadverſions on the Ancent <hi>Greek</hi> and <hi>Latin</hi> Hiſtorians <hi>Oxford</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>212 Apothegms of the Ancients; out of <hi>Plutarch, Macrebius,</hi> &amp;c. <hi>Lond.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>213 <hi>Agrippa (Hen. Corn.)</hi> his Vanity of Arts and Sciences 1676</item>
               <item>214 Argument proving <hi>VVilliam</hi> D. of <hi>Normandy</hi> made no abſolute conqueſt of <hi>Eng.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>215 Account of the late ſiege of <hi>Vienna,</hi> by an Officer in the Town 1684</item>
               <item>216 <hi>Artimedorus</hi> his Interpretation of Dreams 1679</item>
               <item>217 Art of Wheedling or Inſinuation, with the Paſſions of both Sexes 1684</item>
               <item>218 —of Converſe, with the Humors of the <hi>Engliſh</hi> and <hi>French</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>219 Art of Money-catching, or Rules for thriving 1684</item>
               <item>220 <hi>Arcana Aulica,</hi> or <hi>Walſingham</hi>'s Manual of Prudent. Maxims 1652</item>
               <item>221 <hi>Auguſtus,</hi> or the means whereby <hi>Rome</hi> was reduced to a Monarchy 1631</item>
               <item>222 Art of diſcloſing all manner of ſecret Writing, by <hi>J. F.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>223 Apology for Humane Reaſon 1680</item>
               <item>224 <hi>Burne<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi> (Dr. <hi>Gil.</hi>) Abridgment of the Hiſt. of the Reformation (with fig.) 1683</item>
               <item>225 — Hiſtory of the Right of Princes in diſpoſing Church Revenues 1682</item>
               <item>226 Buckler of State and Juſtice againſt the Deſign of Univerſal Monarchy 1667</item>
               <item>227 <hi>Brown</hi> (Sir <hi>Tho.</hi>) his Tracts of the Oracle at <hi>Delphos.</hi> of Propheſie, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>228 Breaches of the King of <hi>France</hi> ſince the Peace of <hi>Nimeguen</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>229 <hi>Bovet (Ric)</hi> Devils Cloyſter, proving the Exiſtence of Witches 1679</item>
               <item>230 <hi>Brown (Tho)</hi> his <hi>Religio Medici,</hi> with Sir <hi>Kel. Digby</hi>'s Obſervations</item>
               <item>231 <hi>Beck (Cave)</hi> Univerſal Character, by which all Nations may underſtand each other 1657</item>
               <item>232 <hi>Bird</hi>'s Magazine of Honour, or Treatiſe of Nob<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>lity 1642</item>
               <item>233 L. <hi>Bacon</hi>'s Remains, Civil, Mor<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>l, Natural Medical, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>234 <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>rle on (VV)</hi> 2 Diſcourſes of the Wits of <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>en, and Myſtery of <hi>Vi<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>tn<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>rs Lond.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>235 <hi>Cotton</hi> (Sir <hi>R<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>b.</hi>) of the power of Parliaments, Liberty of Freemen, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>236 <hi>Cicero</hi>'s 5 Days Debate of Comforts againſt Death, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>237 Critical Hiſtory of the Relig. and Cuſtoms of the <hi>Eaſtern</hi> Nations 1685</item>
               <item>238 <hi>Comm<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>yn (S.)</hi> of the Management and Uſe of of Limon and Orange Trees 1683</item>
               <item>239 Countrey Survey-Book or Land meters <hi>Vade Mecum</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>240 Conference between an Alderman and a Vicar about Oaths 1670</item>
               <item>241 <hi>Chamberlains</hi> Arithmetick, with Tables of Intereſt 1679</item>
               <item>242 Collection of Merchants N<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>mes living in <hi>London</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>243 Civil Wars of <hi>France</hi> during the Reign of <hi>Charles</hi> the Ninth, with Maſſac. in <hi>Paris</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>244 Compleat Servant Maid qualifying them for all Imployments 1680</item>
               <item>245 Courtiers calling, or way of making a Fortune at Court 1675</item>
               <item>246 Councils of Wiſdom, or Collection of the Maxims of <hi>Solomon</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>247 <hi>Cuſanus (C)</hi> His Idiot, or a Treatiſe of Wiſdom <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1650</item>
               <item>248 Conſideration on the lives of <hi>Alci<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>iad<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi> and <hi>C<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="3 letters">
                        <desc>•••</desc>
                     </gap>lanus</hi> 1650</item>
               <item>249 <hi>Chamberlain (Edw.)</hi> Riſe and Fall of Count <hi>Olivares</hi> the <hi>Spaniſh</hi> Impoſtor 1652</item>
               <item>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>50 <hi>Clark (Sam.)</hi> Deſcription of the 17 Provinces of the <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>w Countrys 1672</item>
               <pb n="13" facs="tcp:46599:13"/>
               <item>251 <hi>Cave</hi> (Dr. <hi>Will.</hi>) of Ancient Church Government by Biſhops, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>252 Diſcourſe of Monarchy, for the Succeſſon of the D. of <hi>York</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>253 —Of Supream Power and Common Right by Sir <hi>John Mounſon</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>254 <hi>Delamain</hi> of the Horizontal Quadrant (with Figures)</item>
               <item>255 Diſcourſe of Comets their Original, Subſtances, Preſages, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>256 Diſection of a Libel intituled a Letter about the Black Box 1681</item>
               <item>257 Diſcourſe of the method of well guiding Reaſon 1647</item>
               <item>258 <hi>Downing</hi> (Sir <hi>George</hi>) Diſcourſe againſt the <hi>Hollanders</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>259 Diſcourſe of things above Reaſon, and whether a Philoſopher ſhould admit ſuch 1681</item>
               <item>260 Delights for the Ingenious, or Emblems Divine and Moral 1684</item>
               <item>261 Deſcription of the <hi>Spaniſh</hi> Inquiſition 1683</item>
               <item>262 Eſſay for the Honour of the <hi>Engliſh</hi> Gentry 1684</item>
               <item>263 Eſſay in Moralitie, with the nature of Vertue and Vice. 1682</item>
               <item>264 <hi>England</hi> Deſcribed in its ſeveral Counties and Shires by <hi>E. Leigh</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>265 <hi>Aeſops Fables</hi> engliſhed by <hi>Ogilby</hi> (with curious Figures) 1682</item>
               <item>266 Earl of <hi>Caſtlemains</hi> Account of the Dutch war 1671</item>
               <item>267 <hi>Evelyn (John)</hi> Inſtructions for erecting a Library 1661</item>
               <item>268 Eſtate of the Empire of <hi>Germany</hi> by <hi>Lewis du May</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>269 Engliſh Introduction to the Latin Tongue 1659</item>
               <item>270 Eſſay of thoſe means, by which <hi>Rome</hi> was reduced to a Monarchy 1682</item>
               <item>271 Engliſh Liberties or the Freeborn Subjects Inheritance, by Judge <hi>Yelverton</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>272 <hi>Filmer</hi> (Sir <hi>Rob.</hi>) His works in Defence of Monarchy 1684</item>
               <item>273 <hi>Fuller (Tho.)</hi> His <hi>Andronicus,</hi> or unfortunate <hi>Polititian</hi> 1646</item>
               <item>274 Grand expedient of the Bill of Excluſion, proved contrary to Religion 1685</item>
               <item>275 Grandure of the Law or Collection of Nobility, whoſe Eſtates have been acquir<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ed by the Law 1684</item>
               <item>276 Garden of Engliſh Words, uſeful for teaching of Children to Spell 1683</item>
               <item>277 <hi>Gailhard (J.)</hi> Of ſettlement after Travel and Publick Employments 1682</item>
               <item>278 <hi>Graves (J.)</hi> Diſcription of the Pyramids of <hi>Aegypt</hi> (with Figures) 1646</item>
               <item>279 <hi>Glanvil (Joſ.)</hi> Vanity of Dogmatizing, with an Apology for Philoſophy 1661</item>
               <item>280 <hi>Greorgy (Ed.)</hi> Hiſtorical Anatomy of Chriſtian Melancholly 1646</item>
               <item>281 Hiſtory of the Houſe of <hi>Eſtà,</hi> of which the preſent Queen of <hi>England</hi> is deſcended 1681</item>
               <item>282 —Of Weſt <hi>Barbary</hi> or the Revolutions of <hi>Fez</hi> and <hi>Morocco</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>283 —Of <hi>Philip de Comines</hi> of <hi>Lewis</hi> 11th and <hi>Charles</hi> 8th of <hi>France</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>284 —Of the affairs of <hi>Greece,</hi> in 7 Books by <hi>Xenophon</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>285 —Of the Conſpiracy of <hi>Cateline</hi> againſt <hi>Rome</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>286 —Of Count <hi>Zoſimus</hi> advocate of the Treaſury of the <hi>Roman</hi> Empire 1684</item>
               <item>287 —Of the Wars of the <hi>Jews</hi> by <hi>Joſephus</hi> (with Figures) 1680</item>
               <item>288 —Of the Treaty at <hi>Nimueguen,</hi> with the Intereſt of Europe in that affair 1681</item>
               <item>289 —Of <hi>Scotland</hi> during the minority of King <hi>James,</hi> by <hi>R. Johnſon</hi> 1646</item>
               <item>290 —Of the Lives and Reigns of the Monarchs of <hi>England</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>291 —Of the Court of the King of <hi>China</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>292 —Of the Riſe and Growth of Ancient Ceremonies in the Church 1668</item>
               <item>293 —Of the Government of <hi>Venice,</hi> by S. <hi>R. Amelett</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>294 —Of <hi>Moſcovia,</hi> by <hi>J. Milton</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>295 —Of the Reign of Queen <hi>Mary,</hi> and the Martyrs in her days 168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>296 —Of the Deluſ. Promiſes of the <hi>French,</hi> ſince the <hi>Pyrenean</hi>-Treaty 1685</item>
               <item>297 —Of the Wars of <hi>Hungary</hi> ſince Count <hi>Teckelys</hi> taking up Arms 1685</item>
               <pb n="6" facs="tcp:46599:14"/>
               <item>298 —Of <hi>Hungaria Tranſilvania,</hi> from their Original to 1664 1664</item>
               <item>299 —Of the three Impoſturs <hi>Padre Ottomano, Mahomed Bedi &amp; Sabatai Sevi</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>300 —Of the <hi>Engliſh</hi> and <hi>Scotch</hi> Presbytery, by Dr. <hi>Bazier</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>301 —Of the Holy Prieſthood and Sacrifice of the true Church of Chriſt 1625</item>
               <item>302 Hiſtorical Account of the Antiquities, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of <hi>London</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>303 —Treatiſe of the Prerogatives of the Church of <hi>Rome</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>304 —Rarities and Obſervations, Domeſtick and Foreign 1684</item>
               <item>305 —Collection of the Tranſactions of the two laſt Parliaments 1681</item>
               <item>307 Record of Ancient Hiſtory, intituled <hi>Geſta Romanorum</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>308 Critical Hiſtory of the Relig. and Cuſtoms of the Eaſtern Nations 1685</item>
               <item>309 Hiſtorical and Geographical Deſcription of the <hi>Amazons</hi> in <hi>America</hi> 1666</item>
               <item>310 Hobbs<hi>'s Tripos (viz.)</hi> Elements of Policy, of Law and Lib. and Neceſſity <hi>Lond.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>311 <hi>Hierocles</hi> upon the Golden Verſes of the <hi>Pithagorians</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>312 Help to Diſcourſe or merriment mixt with ſerious matters 1682</item>
               <item>313 Humane Prudence, or Art to Riſe to Grandeur 1682</item>
               <item>314 Horological Dialogues, ſhewing the management of Clocks, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>315 <hi>Hopton (Arthur)</hi> Concordance of years, with the uſe of the <hi>Engl.</hi> and <hi>Rom.</hi> Kal. 1682</item>
               <item>316 <hi>Herle (Ch.)</hi> of Worldly Policy and Moral Prudence 1653</item>
               <item>317 <hi>Hale</hi> (Sir <hi>Matth.</hi>) Contemplations Moral and Divine 1676</item>
               <item>318 Juſtice of Peace his Calling a Moral Eſſay, by Mr. <hi>Bohun</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>319 Inſtructions concerning the Art of Oratory 1684</item>
               <item>320 Journeys to <hi>Jeruſalem,</hi> or Travels of 14 Engliſhmen 1685</item>
               <item>321 Inſtruction for a young Nobleman, or Idea a of Perſon of Honour 1683</item>
               <item>322 Introduction to Aſtrology in three Books, by <hi>J. E.</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>323 Journal of the late Seige of <hi>Vienna,</hi> by an Officer in the Town 1684</item>
               <item>324 Life of <hi>Cyrus</hi> the Great by <hi>Xenophon</hi> of <hi>Athens</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>325 —Of Dr. <hi>Sanderſon</hi> late Biſhop of <hi>Lincoln,</hi> by <hi>Iſaac Walton</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>326 —Of <hi>Julian</hi> with Reflect. on <hi>Johnſon</hi>'s account of his Life 1683</item>
               <item>327 —And Reign of King <hi>Richard</hi> the Second 1681</item>
               <item>328 —Of <hi>Caleb Vernon</hi> an example of Piety 1666</item>
               <item>329 —Of <hi>Chriſtopher Bernard Vangale</hi> Biſhop of Munſter 1680</item>
               <item>330 —Of Sir <hi>Philip Sidney</hi> by Sr. <hi>Fulk Grevil</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>331 —Of the Learned Father <hi>Paul</hi> of the Order of the Service 1651</item>
               <item>332 —And Actions of his Royal Highneſs <hi>James</hi> D. of <hi>York</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>333 —Of the Earl of <hi>Rocheſter,</hi> by Dr. <hi>Gil. Burnet</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>334 —Of Biſhop <hi>Bedel</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>335 Lives of Illuſtrious men, by <hi>C. Nepos,</hi> Engliſhed by ſeveral hands 1684</item>
               <item>336 <hi>Lithgows</hi> Travels through moſt parts of the habitual World 1682</item>
               <item>337 <hi>Laurence (Ric.)</hi> Intereſt of <hi>Ireland,</hi> in Trade and Wealth ſtated 1682</item>
               <item>338 <hi>Leighs</hi> Obſervations on the <hi>Roman</hi> and <hi>Greek</hi> Emperors 1670</item>
               <item>339 <hi>Lithgows</hi> Travles through <hi>Turky, Perſia, E<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ſt India,</hi> &amp;c. 1682</item>
               <item>340 <hi>Lovedays</hi> Letters Domeſtick and Foreign 1684</item>
               <item>341 <hi>Mackenzie</hi> (Sr. <hi>Geo.</hi>) Juſt and Solid foundation of Monarchy 1685</item>
               <item>342 Monarchy Aſſerted in a Conference with <hi>Oliver Cromwel</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>343 Memoirs of the Duke of <hi>Rohan</hi> with Politick Diſcourſes on ſeveral Subjects 1660</item>
               <item>344 <hi>Marvel (And.)</hi> Reherſal Tranſpros'd in Anſwer to Dr. <hi>Parker</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>345 <hi>Majerus (Mick.)</hi> of the ſuperiority of Ceatures under Man 1654</item>
               <item>346 <hi>More</hi> (Dr. <hi>Hen.</hi>) of the Cauſes and Cure of Enthuſiaſm 1645</item>
               <item>347 <hi>March (Jo.)</hi> Actions for Slander 1646
<pb n="7" facs="tcp:46599:14"/>
               </item>
               <item>348 <hi>Meige (Guy)</hi> his Dictionary, <hi>Engliſh</hi> and <hi>French,</hi> and <hi>French</hi> and <hi>Engliſh</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>349 Marriages of Coſin Germans Vindicated <hi>Oxford</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>350 Moral Gallantry, proving Point of Honour obliges to Vertue 1685</item>
               <item>351 Miſchiefs of Rebellion. In three Tracts 1684</item>
               <item>352 Memoirs of the Family of the <hi>Stuarts,</hi> His Majeſties Progenitors 1683</item>
               <item>353 <hi>More</hi> (Sir <hi>Jonas</hi>) Modern Fortifications, or Military Architecture 1673</item>
               <item>354 Merchants Companion, treating of Traffick, Cuſtoms, Coyns, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>355 Monk Unveiled, diſcovering their lewd practices 1678</item>
               <item>356 <hi>Markham</hi>'s Experienced Secrets of 50 years Practice in Horſemanſhip 1684</item>
               <item>357 <hi>Mathews (Ed.)</hi> on the Star that appeared at Kings <hi>Charles</hi>'s Nativity 1662</item>
               <item>358 <hi>More</hi> (Sir <hi>Tho.</hi>) his Commonwealth of <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>topia</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>359 <hi>Mackenzie (Geo.)</hi> Defence of the Antiq. of the Royal Line of <hi>Scotland</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>360 <hi>Malvezzi</hi>'s <hi>(Virgil.)</hi> Romulus and Tarquin 1648</item>
               <item>361 <hi>Nye (Nath.)</hi> Art of Gunnery, taking Heights, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> (with Figures) 1670</item>
               <item>362 Optick Glaſs of Humours, by <hi>T. W.</hi> 1637</item>
               <item>363 Opinions of Mr. <hi>Hobbs</hi> conſidered, by Dr. <hi>Etchard</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>364 <hi>Pettit. (William)</hi> Ancient Right of the Commons of <hi>England</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>365 — <hi>(Ed.)</hi> Viſions of Purgatory, diſcovering the Errors of the Papiſts 1685</item>
               <item>366 — Viſions of Government, againſt Antimonarchical Principles 1684</item>
               <item>367 <hi>Plato</hi>'s Demon, or the State-Phiſitian Unmasked 1684</item>
               <item>368 Prerogative of Primogeniture in an Hereditary Crown 1685</item>
               <item>369 Pernicious Conſequencies of the Hereſie of the Jeſuits againſt King and State 1666</item>
               <item>370 <hi>Pontier (Gid.)</hi> Survey of the Preſent State of <hi>Europe</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>371 Policy of the Clergy of <hi>France</hi> to deſtroy the Proteſtants 1681</item>
               <item>372 Policy and Government of the <hi>Venetians</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>373 Philoſophical Diſcourſe concerning Speech 1668</item>
               <item>374 <hi>Patriarcha,</hi> or the Natural Power of Kings, by Sir <hi>Rob. Filmer</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>375 Queries concerning the Revolution of Humane Souls 1684</item>
               <item>376 Revolutions of the Kingdoms of <hi>Fez</hi> and <hi>Morocco,</hi> by <hi>Addiſon Lond.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>377 <hi>Ray (J.)</hi> Collection of <hi>Engliſh</hi> and <hi>Scotch</hi> Proverbs 1678</item>
               <item>378 Royal Buckler, or a Lecture to the Murtherers of King <hi>Charles</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>379 Rehearſal Tranſpros'd, or Animadverſions on Dr. <hi>Parker</hi>'s Preface 1613</item>
               <item>380 Relation of the River <hi>Nile,</hi> its Sourſe, Current, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>381 Reflections on the Eloquence of the Bar and Pulpit 1612</item>
               <item>382 <hi>Roſs (Alex.)</hi> his Animadverſions on <hi>Hobbs</hi>'s <hi>Leviathan</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>383 State of <hi>England,</hi> in Two Parts, by Dr. <hi>Ed. Chamberlain</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>384 — <hi>Idem,</hi> with a Third and Fourth Part, by another Author, in 2 Vol. 1684</item>
               <item>385 — Of <hi>Scotland</hi> with Reflections on the Ancient State thereof 1682</item>
               <item>386 — Of the United Provinces of the <hi>Low Countreys</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>387 — Of <hi>Denmark,</hi> by <hi>Guy Miege</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>388 — Of <hi>Denmark,</hi> with an ccount of the Birth of Prince <hi>George</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>389 — Of <hi>London,</hi> by <hi>Tho. De Laune</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>390 — Of the <hi>Jews,</hi> with their Cuſtoms Secular and Religious 1680</item>
               <item>391 — Of <hi>Jamacia,</hi> with the Life of <hi>Columbus</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>392 — Of <hi>Ruſſia,</hi> by a Perſon reſiding at the <hi>Czars</hi> Court at <hi>Moſco</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>393 Strange and Prodigious Religions of ſundry Nations 1683</item>
               <item>394 Secret Services of <hi>Monſieur de Vernay</hi> to Count <hi>Teekely</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>395 <hi>Scudery</hi>'s Converſations upon ſeveral Subjects 1683</item>
               <item>396 School of Princes or the Conſpiracy preceeding the Death of <hi>Alexander</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>397 Slaughter-houſe, or Deſcription of the <hi>Spaniſh</hi> Inquiſition 1683</item>
               <pb n="16" facs="tcp:46599:15"/>
               <item>398 <hi>Smith</hi> (Sir <hi>Tho.</hi>) Commonwealth of <hi>England</hi> 1635</item>
               <item>399 Survey of the affairs of the <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>nited Netherlands</hi> 1665</item>
               <item>400 <hi>Seymar (Will.) Conjugium Conjurgium,</hi> or Conſideration on Marriage 1675</item>
               <item>401 <hi>Sprat</hi>'s Obſervations on <hi>Sorbiers</hi> Voyage into <hi>England</hi> 1665</item>
               <item>402 <hi>Selden (John)</hi> Tract on the Birth-day of our Saviour 1661</item>
               <item>403 Treatiſe of Settlement after Travel, and publick Imployments, by <hi>Gailhard</hi> 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>2</item>
               <item>404 Treatiſe of Liberty and Servitude, Tranſlated out of <hi>French Lond.</hi> 1641</item>
               <item>405 Trial of the 29 Regicides, or Murthers of K. <hi>Charles</hi> the Firſt <hi>Lond.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>406 <hi>Tully</hi>'s Offices, <hi>Engliſhed</hi> by Sir <hi>Roger L'Eſtrange</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>407 <hi>Trenchfield (Caleb)</hi> Advice to his Son an Apprentice in <hi>London</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>408 Treatiſe of Loftineſs and Elegancy of Speech 1680</item>
               <item>409 <hi>Temple</hi> (Sir <hi>Will.</hi>) Obſervations on the <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>nited Netherlands</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>410 Tranſproſer Rehearſed on the fifth Act of <hi>Bays</hi>'s Play 1673</item>
               <item>411 Vindication of the Primitive Chriſtians againſt <hi>Johnſon</hi>'s Life of <hi>Julian</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>412 Voyages of Capt. <hi>Booth, Sharp</hi> and others in the <hi>South-Sea</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>413 Unheard of Curioſities of the reading of the Stars, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>Gaffarel</hi> 1650</item>
               <item>414 Voyage to the <hi>Levant,</hi> by Sir <hi>Henry Blunt</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>415 Vermin-killer, or Rules for killing Rats, Mice, Moles, Serpents, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>416 <hi>Wheare (Deg.)</hi> Method and Order of Reading both Civil and Eccleſiaſtical Hiſtories with an appendix concerning the Hiſtorians of particular Na<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tions 1685</item>
               <item>417 <hi>Wharton (George)</hi> his Works in Aſtronomy, Palmeſtry, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>418 <hi>Walker (Joſ.)</hi> Treatiſe of Teleſcopes, with the Diſcoveries made by them 1684</item>
               <item>419 Witt againſt wiſdom or a Panegyrick on Folly, by <hi>Eraſmus</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>420 Way to Promotion, or Young mans Guide to perferment 1682</item>
               <item>421 Woman as good as the Man, or equality of both Sexes 1667</item>
               <item>422 <hi>Whitlock (Ric.)</hi> Obſervation on the preſent manners of the Engliſh 1654</item>
               <item>423 <hi>Wingate (Ed.)</hi> Nat. Arithmetick and Tables of Logarithmes 1630</item>
               <item>424 <hi>Wharton (Geo.)</hi> Art of Divining by the Lines of the Hand 1652</item>
               <item>425 <hi>Waſe (Chr.)</hi> Dictionary, Engliſh Latine, and Latine Engliſh 1675</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="list">
            <head>Law in Octavo and Twelves.</head>
            <list>
               <item>426 ARugment proving that <hi>William</hi> Duke of <hi>Normandy</hi> made no abſolute Con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>queſt of <hi>England</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>427 <hi>Brown (T.)</hi> of Ancient tenures of Lands and Cuſtoms of Mannors 1684</item>
               <item>428 <hi>Hales</hi> (Sir <hi>Matth.</hi>) Pleas of the Crown 1685</item>
               <item>429 Judge <hi>Jenkin</hi>'s Works about the Liberty of the Subject, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>430 <hi>Lambard (Will.)</hi> Duty and Office of Conſtables and Church Wardens 1677</item>
               <item>431 <hi>Noy (Will.)</hi> Grounds and Maxims of the Laws of <hi>England</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>432 Practice of Spiritual and Eccleſiaſtical Courts, by <hi>H. C.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>433 <hi>Pettit (Will.)</hi> Ancient Rights of the Commons of <hi>England</hi> Aſſerted 1680</item>
               <item>434 <hi>Pettus</hi> (Sr. <hi>John</hi>) Conſtitution of the Parliaments of <hi>England</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>435 Parſons Law, or the Law of Tythes, by <hi>William Hughes</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>436 <hi>Wingates</hi> Body of the Common Law of <hi>England</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>437 <hi>Williams (W.)</hi> of the Power to releaſe unjuſt Decrees in Chancery 1683</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="list">
            <pb n="9" facs="tcp:46599:15"/>
            <head>Phyſick, Philoſophy, &amp;c. <hi>Folio.</hi>
            </head>
            <list>
               <item>1 <hi>B<g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>rton</hi>'s Anatomy of Melancholly with its Cauſes and Cure <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1524</item>
               <item>2 <hi>Bonet (Theo.)</hi> Guide to the practical Phiſitian <hi>Lond.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>3 <hi>Bacons</hi> Natural Hiſtory with the Hiſtory of Life and Death 1683</item>
               <item>4 <hi>Brown</hi>'s (Dr. <hi>Tho.</hi>) Enquires in Vulgar and Common Errors 1683</item>
               <item>5 <hi>Crooke (Helk.)</hi> Deſcription of the Body of Man (with Figures) 1631</item>
               <item>6 Country Farm, or a Treatiſe of Agriculture, by <hi>Gervaſe Markham</hi> 1616</item>
               <item>7 Diſtiller of <hi>London,</hi> ſet forth by the Kings Command 1639</item>
               <item>8 <hi>Evelin</hi>'s <hi>Silva</hi> or a Diſcourſe of Foreſt Trees 1679</item>
               <item>9 French Academy in 4 Books, by <hi>Peter de la Primaudage</hi> 1618</item>
               <item>10 <hi>Geſner (Con.)</hi> Hiſtory of fourfooted Beaſts and Serpents (with Figures) 1658</item>
               <item>11 <hi>Grew (Nich.)</hi> Anatomy of Plants, Roots and (with Figures) 1682</item>
               <item>12 <hi>Hart (James)</hi> Diet of the Diſeaſed, ſhewing what meats are moſt proper for the Sick 1683</item>
               <item>13 <hi>Leybourn (Will.)</hi> Compleat Surveyor, or art of ſurveying Land 1657</item>
               <item>14 Miſtery of Husbandry, with new ways of Tilling, Planting, Sowing, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>15 <hi>Parkinſon (John)</hi> his Univerſal and Compleat Herbal 1640</item>
               <item>16 —Garden of Flowers, their Nature and place of Birth 1656</item>
               <item>17 Royal and Practical Chimiſtry, by <hi>Crollius</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>18 <hi>Snape (Andrew)</hi> Anatomy of an Horſe (with Figures) 1683</item>
               <item>19 <hi>Syſtema Agriculturae,</hi> or the Miſtery of Husbandry 1681</item>
               <item>20 <hi>Van Helmonts</hi> Works in Philoſ. Phyſ. Chirurgery and Anatomy 1664</item>
               <item>21 <hi>Willis (Tho.)</hi> 2 Diſcourſes of the Souls of Brutes 1683</item>
               <item>22 <hi>Wilkins</hi> (Biſhop <hi>John</hi>) Real Character and Philoſophical Language 1668</item>
               <item>23 <hi>Willougby (Francis)</hi> Deſcription of all ſorts of Birds (with Figures) with the or<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dering of Singing Birds 1678</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="list">
            <head>Phyſick, Philoſophy, &amp;c. <hi>Quarto.</hi>
            </head>
            <list>
               <item>24 <hi>ATwel (Geo.)</hi> Faithful Surveyor or Art of Meaſuring Land <hi>Lond.</hi> 1648</item>
               <item>25 <hi>Boyle (Rob.)</hi> Phyſiological Eſſays on ſeveral occaſions 1661</item>
               <item>26 <hi>Barrough (Philip)</hi> Method of Phyſick, with cures for ſeveral Diſeaſes 1639</item>
               <item>27 <hi>Bruges (Tho.)</hi> Marrow of Phyſick, and way of making moſt Medicines 1669</item>
               <item>28 <hi>Cook (Moſes)</hi> Manner of ordering Foreſt and Fruit Trees 1679</item>
               <item>29 <hi>Charlton (Will.)</hi> Enquiries into humane Nature 1680</item>
               <item>30 <hi>Digby</hi> (Sir <hi>Ken.</hi>) Of the nature of Bodys, and Immortality of Souls 1645</item>
               <item>31 <hi>Dereys</hi> Compleat Horſeman, or Breeding, Riding, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of Horſes 1684</item>
               <item>32 <hi>Foſter (Will.)</hi> Againſt the uſe of Weapon Salve, with <hi>Fluds</hi> Anſwer 1631</item>
               <item>33 <hi>French (John)</hi> His Art of Diſtellation, with the <hi>London</hi> Diſtiller 1667</item>
               <item>34 <hi>Le Febures</hi> Compleat Body of Chimiſtry 1664</item>
               <item>35 <hi>Power (Hen.)</hi> His Experimental Philoſophy, in 3 Books 1664</item>
               <item>36 <hi>Purchas (Sam.)</hi> Of the Nature and right ordering of Bees 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>7</item>
               <item>37 <hi>Read (Alex.)</hi> Chirurgical Lectures of Tumours and Ulcers 1635</item>
               <item>38 <hi>Venner (Tho.)</hi> way of obtaining Health and long Life. 1650</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="list">
            <pb n="10" facs="tcp:46599:16"/>
            <head>
               <hi>Phyſick, Chirurgery, Cookery, &amp;c.</hi> in Octavo and Twelves.</head>
            <list>
               <item>39 ARt of Phyſick made plain and eaſie, by <hi>Frambeſarius</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>40 Anatomy of the Elder, with its Remedies for moſt Diſeaſes 1677</item>
               <item>41 <hi>Brown (John)</hi> of the Kings Evil, and the Royal gift of Healing 1684</item>
               <item>42 <hi>Bacon (Roger)</hi> his Cure of Old age and Preſervation of Youth 1683</item>
               <item>43 <hi>Barbette (Paul)</hi> his Practice of Phyſick 1675</item>
               <item>44 <hi>Blanchard (S.)</hi> Phyſical Dictionary, Explaining Terms in Anat. Surgery, Chi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>miſtry, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>45</item>
               <item>46 <hi>Boyle (Rob.)</hi> Natural Hiſtory of Humane Blood 1684</item>
               <item>47 —Experiments touching the Spring of Air 1660</item>
               <item>48 —Experimental Hiſtory of Colours 1664</item>
               <item>49 —Hydorſtatical Paradoxes 1666</item>
               <item>50 —Experimental Hiſtory of Cold with an Account of Freezing 1665</item>
               <item>51 —Tracts of the Coſmical Qualities of Things, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>52 <hi>Bunworth (R.)</hi> Directions for Curing the French Diſeaſe 1662</item>
               <item>53 <hi>Burgis (Tho.)</hi> Companion for a Surgeon, fitted for Sea and Land 1681</item>
               <item>54 <hi>Blagraves</hi> Introduction to Aſtrology, with the Method of Judging Nativities 1682</item>
               <item>55 Book of Palmeſtry or inſtructions to manual divination</item>
               <item>56 Book of Knowledge, ſhewing the effects of the Planets 1683</item>
               <item>57 Compleat Midwifes Practice, enlarged with Sr. <hi>Theod. Mayernes</hi> Secrets 1680</item>
               <item>58 <hi>Charas (H.)</hi> Experiments upon Vipers, with Remedies drawn from them 1673</item>
               <item>59 Compendium of Surgery, containing its Grounds and Principels 1683</item>
               <item>60 <hi>Culpeper (Nich.)</hi> Medicaments for the Poor 1673</item>
               <item>61 —<hi>London</hi> Diſpenſitory 1679</item>
               <item>62 —Engliſh Phyſitian</item>
               <item>63 Country mans Phyſitian, ſhewing the Cure of moſt Diſeaſes 1680</item>
               <item>64 <hi>Clark (Will.)</hi> Natural Hiſtory of <hi>Nitre,</hi> with its Vertues and Uſes 1670</item>
               <item>65 <hi>Cook (James)</hi> Select Obſervations on Engliſh Bodys 1657</item>
               <item>66 <hi>Coles (Will.)</hi> Art of Simpling, or Knowledge of Plants 1657</item>
               <item>67 <hi>Chambers</hi> Diſcourſe of the Principles of Chiromancy 1658</item>
               <item>68 <hi>Digby</hi> (Sr. <hi>Kenelm</hi>) His Recepts in Phyſick Chirurgery 1675</item>
               <item>69 <hi>Digby</hi> (Sr. <hi>Kenelm</hi>) Chimical Secrets and Experiments (with Figures) 1683</item>
               <item>70 —Directions for Cookery, Preſerving, Candying, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>71 Direction of Significative Muſcles of the affections, by <hi>J. B.</hi> 1649</item>
               <item>72 <hi>Falk (W.)</hi> of Meteors, with the cauſes of Thunder, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>73 <hi>Grew (Nich.</hi> Anatomy of Vegetables, and Account of Vegetation <hi>Lond.</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>74 —Philological Hiſtory of Roots, and their Vegetation 1673</item>
               <item>75 —Comparative Anatomy of Trunks (with Figures) 1674</item>
               <item>76 <hi>Graafs</hi> Treatiſe of the Nature and office of Pancreatick Juice 1676</item>
               <item>77 <hi>Haworth (Sam.)</hi> Diſcription of the Dukes Bagnio, with the uſe of Sweating, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>78 —True Method of Curing Conſumptions 1683</item>
               <item>79 <hi>Harvey (Gid.)</hi> Little Venus Unmasked 1685</item>
               <item>80 —Diſcourſe of the Small-Pox and Malignant Fevers 1683</item>
               <item>81 —Conclave of Phiſitians detecting their Frauds 1683</item>
               <item>82 —Anatomy of Conſumptions, with diſc<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="3 letters">
                     <desc>•••</desc>
                  </gap>ſes of Melancholly, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>83 —Practical Treatiſe of Fevers 1674</item>
               <item>84 <hi>Heydon (Chr.)</hi> of the Influence of the Pl<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="3 letters">
                     <desc>•••</desc>
                  </gap>ts o<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> Elementary Bodies 1650</item>
               <pb n="11" facs="tcp:46599:16"/>
               <item>84 Dr. <hi>Harris</hi> hs Rational Diſcourſe of Remedies in Phyſick againſt Empyricks and Mounebanks 1683</item>
               <item>85 Intereſt of the Patient in reference to Phyſick and Phyſitians, by Dr. <hi>Cox</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>86 <hi>Johnſon (Rob.</hi> Manual of Phyſick, or Compend. of the whole Art 1684</item>
               <item>87 Introduction to the whole Practice of Phyſick 1685</item>
               <item>88 <hi>Johnſon (Will)</hi> animadverſions on <hi>Tompſon</hi> about Blood-letting 1665</item>
               <item>89 <hi>Lovel</hi>'s Hiſtory of Animals and Minerals 1661</item>
               <item>90 <hi>Mainwaring (Ever.)</hi> of the Scurvy, its nature and Cure <hi>Lond.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>91 — Method of enjoying Health and long life 1683</item>
               <item>92 —of Pai<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>s with a Tract of Iſſues and Setons 1682</item>
               <item>93 New myſtery of curing Fevers and Agues by Jeſuits Powder 168</item>
               <item>94 New ligh<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> of Alchimy with a Chimical Dictionary <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>74</item>
               <item>95 <hi>Organon Salutis,</hi> or an Inſtrument to cleanſe the Stomach 1659</item>
               <item>96 <hi>Plat (Hugh)</hi> Garden of <hi>Eden,</hi> or Deſcription of Flowers and Fruits 1660</item>
               <item>97 Preſerver and Reſtorer of Health, or Receipts in Cookery and Phyſick 1684</item>
               <item>98 <hi>Pemel (Rob.) Medicamen miſeris</hi> or Phyſick for the Poor 1650</item>
               <item>99 <hi>Philalethes (Eug.)</hi> Confeſſion of the fraternity of the <hi>Roſie Cros</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>100 —his Natural Hiſtory 1669</item>
               <item>101 Rules of Health in eight Sections of Aphoriſms, by <hi>Sanctorius</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>102 <hi>Ryder (H.)</hi> Practical Obſervations in Surgery 1685</item>
               <item>103 <hi>Rowland (Will.)</hi> Treatiſe of Wind offending mans body 1676</item>
               <item>104 <hi>Record (Rob.)</hi> Urinal Phyſick, or Judicial Urines 1665</item>
               <item>105 <hi>Ramſey (Will.)</hi> Treatiſe of the ſundry ſorts and natures of Poyſons 1661</item>
               <item>106 <hi>Riverius (Lazarus)</hi> His Secrets in Phyſick 1685</item>
               <item>107 <hi>Sylvius le Boe</hi> of Childrens Diſeaſes, Jaundice, Gripes, Rickets, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>108 <hi>Sennertus</hi> his Practical Phyſick, <hi>Engliſhed</hi> by <hi>N. Culpeper</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>109 <hi>Saunders (Rich.)</hi> his Palmiſtry with Obſervations of Phiſiognomy 1676</item>
               <item>110 The Doctors Phyſitian, or Dialogues concerning Health 1685</item>
               <item>111 The Man-Midwife, comprehending the whole Body of Midwifry 1664</item>
               <item>112 <hi>Thibaut (P.)</hi> his Art of Chimiſtry, as it is now practiſed 1675</item>
               <item>113 <hi>Thomſon (Geo.)</hi> Chimical trial of the Galeniſts about Blood-letting 1665</item>
               <item>114 Uncertainty of the Art of Phyſick, with the abuſes practiſed by its Profeſſors 1684</item>
               <item>115 <hi>VVood (Owen)</hi> Alphabetical Book of Phyſical Secrets 1639</item>
               <item>116 <hi>Wharton</hi> (Sir <hi>Geo.</hi>) his Works in Aſtronomy and Palmiſtry, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>117 Dr. <hi>Willis</hi> his Practice of Phyſick 1685</item>
               <item>118 <hi>Angler Vade Mecum,</hi> or a Diſcourſe of Angling 1681</item>
               <item>119 Art of Pruning Fruit-Trees, with an Explanation of Gardiners Terms 1685</item>
               <item>120 <hi>Commelyn</hi> of the management and uſe of Lemmon and Orange-Trees 1683</item>
               <item>121 Compleat Planter and Cyderiſt, with Obſervations on Fruit-Trees 1685</item>
               <item>122 Country mans Guide for curing and breeding of Cattel 1679</item>
               <item>123 Compleat Angler, or Inſtructions for Angling 1679</item>
               <item>124 Experienced Angler or Angling improved, by <hi>R. Venables</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>125 <hi>Evelyns Kalendarium Hortenſe,</hi> or Gardiners Almanack 1683</item>
               <item>126 Husbandmans Magazine, or Directions for breeding Cattel 1684</item>
               <item>127 Gentlemans Tutor to Hunting, Racing, Hawking, Shooting, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>128 <hi>Maſcall (L.)</hi> of the Government of all ſorts of Cattel 1680</item>
               <item>129 <hi>Markhams</hi> Experienced Secrets of fifty years Practice in Horſemanſhip 1684</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="list">
            <pb n="12" facs="tcp:46599:17"/>
            <head>Treatiſes of Waters, <hi>Octavo.</hi>
            </head>
            <list>
               <item>130 <hi>DEerham</hi>'s account of <hi>Iſlington</hi>-Waters, with Directions for drinking them 1685</item>
               <item>131 Dr. <hi>French</hi>'s Treatiſe of the <hi>Yorkshire</hi> Spaw 1654</item>
               <item>132 Dr. <hi>Guidot</hi>'s Obſervations on the Hot Waters at <hi>Bath</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>133 Dr. <hi>Wittie</hi> of the nature and vertue of the <hi>Scarborough</hi> Spaw, and other waters in general, and of <hi>Vincent</hi>'s Waters in ſpecial 1660</item>
               <item>134 Dr. <hi>Wittie</hi> againſt <hi>Tonſtall</hi> about the <hi>Scarborough</hi>-Spaw 1672</item>
               <item>135 Dr. <hi>Simpſon</hi>'s Anatomy of the <hi>Scarborough</hi>-Spaw, and other Spaws in <hi>Yorkshire,</hi> with a Diſcourſe of the original of Hot Springs and Fountains 1669</item>
               <item>136 Obſervations on the Mineral Waters of <hi>France</hi> made in the Royal Academy of Sciences 1684</item>
               <item>137 Dr. <hi>Walker</hi>'s Meditations on Fountains and Waters</item>
               <item>138 Eſquire <hi>Boyle</hi>'s Memoirs for Natural and Experimental Hiſtory of Mineral Waters</item>
               <item>139 Dr. <hi>Rowzee</hi> of the Nature and Vertues of <hi>Tunbridge</hi>-Waters 1671</item>
               <item>140 Dr. <hi>Rich. Short</hi> of Drinking Water, and of Warm Drink 1656</item>
               <item>141 Dr. <hi>Whitaker</hi>'s Diſcourſe of Waters, their Qualities, Effects, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1634</item>
               <item>142 Dr. <hi>Jones</hi> Diſcourſe of Baths, of Baths-Ayd, and of <hi>Buckſtone</hi>'s in <hi>Darbyſhire</hi> 1572</item>
               <item>143 <hi>Latham</hi>'s-Spaw in <hi>Lancaſhire,</hi> with the Cures effected by it 1672</item>
               <item>144 Treatiſe of the ancient Medicinal or Vitrioline-Spaw near <hi>Durham</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>145 <hi>Jordain</hi>'s Diſcourſe of Baths and Mineral-Waters 16</item>
               <item>146 <hi>Porter</hi>'s Treatiſe of <hi>Leviſham</hi> or <hi>Dulwich</hi>-Wells in <hi>Kent</hi> 1680</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="list">
            <head>Poetry, Plays, Romances, Novels, &amp;c. <hi>Fol.</hi>
            </head>
            <list>
               <item>1 A Almahide or the Captive Queen a Romance by <hi>Monſieur de Scudery—Lond.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>2 <hi>Boccalin</hi>'s Advertiſements from <hi>Parnaſſus,</hi> with the Politick Touchſtone 1674</item>
               <item>3 <hi>Bowman (H.)</hi> his Songs with muſical Notes <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>4 <hi>Boccacio (John)</hi> 100 Curious Novels and Tales <hi>Lond.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>5 <hi>Bentivolio</hi> and <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>rama</hi> in ſix Books, by <hi>Nath. Ingelo</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>6 <hi>Chaucer (Geffrey)</hi> Works of Antient Poetry, with his Life and expoſition of his Terms 1598</item>
               <item>7</item>
               <item>8 <hi>Cowleys</hi> Poems and other works</item>
               <item>9 <hi>Chapman (Geo.)</hi> his Tranſlation of <hi>Homers Illiads</hi>
               </item>
               <item>10 Counteſs of <hi>Pembroks</hi> Arcadia, with other works by Sir <hi>Philip Sidney</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>11 <hi>Clelia</hi> a Romance, <hi>Monſieur de Scudery</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>12 <hi>Coralbo</hi> A Romance by <hi>F. B<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ondi</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>13 <hi>Davenant</hi> (Sr. <hi>Will.</hi>) his Works (Plays and Poems) 1673</item>
               <item>14 <hi>Fulk</hi> Lord <hi>Brooks</hi> his Poems, Plays and Letters 1633</item>
               <item>15 <hi>Juvenal</hi> and <hi>Perſius</hi> Tranſlated and illuſtrated, with Notes and Sculpt. by <hi>B. Holliday</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>16 <hi>Johnſon (Ben.)</hi> his Plays in 2 Volumes 1640</item>
               <item>17 <hi>Ibrahim,</hi> or the Illuſtrious Baſſa a Romance, by <hi>Scudery</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>18 <hi>Marvell</hi>'s <hi>(Andr.)</hi> Miſcellaneous Poems 1681</item>
               <item>19 <hi>Orlando Furioſo,</hi> by Sir <hi>John Harrington,</hi> (with Figures) 1673</item>
               <pb n="25" facs="tcp:46599:17"/>
               <item>20 <hi>Bayly</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Wall-flower, an Hiſtory partly true, partly Romantick 1679</item>
               <item>21 <hi>Phillips</hi> (Mrs. <hi>Kath.</hi>) her Poems</item>
               <item>22 <hi>Reynolds (John)</hi> Gods Revenge againſt Murther and Adultery (with Figures.) 1679</item>
               <item>23 <hi>Spencer (Edmund)</hi> his Works, <hi>viz.</hi> Fairy Queen, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>24 <hi>Shakeſpear (Will.)</hi> his Comedies, Hiſtories, and Tragedies 1685</item>
               <item>25 City Match, a Comedy <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1639</item>
               <item>26 Wild-Gooſe Chaſe, a Comedy by <hi>Beaumont</hi> and <hi>Fletcher London.</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>27 <hi>Juvenal</hi>'s Satyrs <hi>Engliſhed</hi> and Illuſtrated with Figures, by <hi>Rob. Stapleton</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>28 <hi>John Taylor</hi> the Water-Poet, his Works 1630</item>
            </list>
            <div type="list">
               <head>Quarto.</head>
               <list>
                  <item>29 <hi>Argalus</hi> and <hi>Parthenia,</hi> a Poem, by <hi>F. Quarles</hi> (with Figures) 1684</item>
                  <item>30 <hi>Barclay (John)</hi> his <hi>Argenis, Engliſhed</hi> by Sir <hi>Rob. le Grys</hi> 1629</item>
                  <item>31 <hi>Grecian</hi> Story, an Hiſtorical Poem, by <hi>J. H.</hi> Eſq; 1684</item>
                  <item>32 <hi>Woodford (Sam.)</hi> Paraphraſe on the <hi>Pſalms</hi> of <hi>David</hi> 1667</item>
               </list>
            </div>
            <div type="list">
               <head>Octavo.</head>
               <list>
                  <item>33 Academy of Complements, with a Collection of Songs 1681</item>
                  <item>34 Academy of Eloquence, by <hi>T. Blount,</hi> Eſq;, 1683</item>
                  <item>35 Academical Diſcourſes upon Pleaſant Subjects, by <hi>J. B.</hi> 1664</item>
                  <item>36 <hi>Aſtrea,</hi> or the Grove of Beatitude (with Figures) 1665</item>
                  <item>37 <hi>Boccacio (John)</hi> his Novels 1634</item>
                  <item>38 Compleat Gameſter, or Rules for playing at all Games 1680</item>
                  <item>39 <hi>Cimmerian Matron,</hi> a Novel, with the Myſteries and Miracles of Love 1684</item>
                  <item>40 Coffee-Houſe Jeſts 1682</item>
                  <item>41 <hi>Cambridge</hi> Jeſts 1684</item>
                  <item>42 Canting Academy, with new Catches and Songs 1674</item>
                  <item>43 Compleat Academy, or a Nurſery of Complements 1676</item>
                  <item>44 <hi>Don Tomazo,</hi> or the Juvenile Rambles of <hi>Tho. Dangerfield</hi> 1680</item>
                  <item>45 Delightful Novels, or Stories of Amours Tragical and Comical 1685</item>
                  <item>46 <hi>Aeſop</hi>'s Fables, <hi>Engliſhed</hi> by <hi>J. Ogilby</hi> (with Figures) 1683</item>
                  <item>47 Elegies written by divers Perſons, on the death of the Lord <hi>Haſtings</hi> 1649</item>
                  <item>48 <hi>French</hi> Rogue, his Life and Adventures 1672</item>
                  <item>49 Fifteen real Comforts of Matrimony 1683</item>
                  <item>50 Hiſtory of <hi>Auriſtella,</hi> with pleaſant ſtories of <hi>Paul</hi> of <hi>Segonia London</hi> 1683</item>
                  <item>51 Help to Diſcourſe, or Merriment mixt with ſerious Matters 1682</item>
                  <item>52 Hiſtory of the Seven Wiſe Maſters of <hi>Rome</hi> 1683</item>
                  <item>53 — Of the pleaſant Adventures of <hi>Fortunatus</hi> 1682</item>
                  <item>54 Love Letters from a Cavalier, in Anſwer to a Nuns Letters 1683</item>
                  <item>55 <hi>Middleton (Tho.)</hi> No Wit like a Womans, a Comedy 1657</item>
                  <item>56 — <hi>(John)</hi> his Poems 1645</item>
                  <item>57 <hi>Overbury</hi> (Sir <hi>Tho.</hi>) his Life and Character 1628</item>
                  <item>58 Obſervations on the Poems of <hi>Homer</hi> and <hi>Virgil</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>59 Poor <hi>Robbin</hi>'s Viſions, deſcribing the Humours of the Times 1677</item>
                  <item>60 Pleaſant Companion, or Collection of Ingenious Stories</item>
                  <item>61 <hi>Quevedo</hi>'s Viſions of Hell, the World, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1668</item>
                  <item>62 Poems <hi>(viz.)</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>63 <hi>Anacreon,</hi> done into <hi>Engliſh</hi> out of the Original <hi>Greek Oxford</hi> 1683</item>
                  <item>64 <hi>Aminta,</hi> or the Famous Poſtoral, a Poem <hi>London</hi> 1660</item>
                  <item>65 Satyrs upon the Jeſuits, by <hi>Oldham</hi> 1682</item>
                  <item>66 Poems on ſeveral Occaſions, by <hi>Oldham</hi> 1681</item>
                  <item>67 Collection of Poems on ſeveral Occaſions, by ſeveral Perſons 1673</item>
                  <pb n="26" facs="tcp:46599:18"/>
                  <item>68 Songs of <hi>Moſes</hi> and <hi>Deborah</hi> Paraphraſed, with other Poems 1685</item>
                  <item>69 Poems on the Rules of the Nouns and Verbs 1682</item>
                  <item>70 Wit and Drollery, Jovial Poems 1682</item>
                  <item>71 <hi>Suckling</hi> (Sir <hi>John</hi>) his Poems and Letters 1659</item>
                  <item>72 <hi>Hudibras,</hi> a Poem on the late Wars, in three Parts compleat 1684</item>
                  <item>73 <hi>Flatman (Tho.)</hi> his Poems and Songs 1682</item>
                  <item>74 Poems on ſeveral Occaſions, by Mrs. <hi>A. Behn</hi> 1684</item>
                  <item>75 Collection of Songs and Poems, by <hi>Tho. Durfey</hi> 1683</item>
                  <item>76 Poems Panegyrical, Satyrical, and Ironical, by <hi>P. K.</hi> 1684</item>
                  <item>77 Poems, Songs, and Love-Verſes, by M <hi>Coppinger</hi> 1682</item>
                  <item>78 <hi>Scarronides,</hi> a Mock-Poem on <hi>Virgil</hi>'s firſt four <hi>Aeneids</hi> 1682</item>
                  <item>79 <hi>Maronides,</hi> a Mock-Poem on <hi>Virgil</hi>'s fifth and ſixth <hi>Aeneid</hi> 1672</item>
                  <item>80 Poems on ſeveral Occaſions, by <hi>Edmund Waller</hi> 1682</item>
                  <item>81 The Wonders of the <hi>Peak</hi> in <hi>Darby-ſhire,</hi> a Poem, by <hi>Tho. Hobbs</hi> 1683</item>
                  <item>82 Gallantry Al-a-mode, a Satyrical Poem 1674</item>
                  <item>83 <hi>Holborn</hi> Drollery, or Songs and Poems 1673</item>
                  <item>84 <hi>Troades</hi> in <hi>Engliſh</hi> Verſe, by <hi>S. P.</hi> 1660</item>
                  <item>85 Poetical Honey gathered out of the Weeds of <hi>Parnaſſus,</hi> by <hi>Roſſe</hi> 1642</item>
                  <item>86 Poems by <hi>Michael Drayton</hi> 1637</item>
                  <item>87 <hi>Flamma ſine fumo,</hi> or Poems without Fictions, by <hi>R. W.</hi> 1662</item>
                  <item>88 <hi>Ovid</hi>'s <hi>Metamorphoſis,</hi> rendred into <hi>Engliſh</hi> Verſe by <hi>Sandys</hi> 1678</item>
                  <item>89 <hi>Lucan</hi>'s <hi>Pharſalia,</hi> rendred into <hi>Engliſh</hi> Verſe by <hi>T. May</hi> 1650</item>
                  <item>90 Wits Recreation, or Epigrams, Fancies, Fantaſticks, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1683</item>
                  <item>91 <hi>Howard</hi> (Sir <hi>Rob.</hi>) his Poems and Tranſlations 1660</item>
                  <item>92 <hi>Lovelace (Rich.)</hi> his Poems. 1639</item>
                  <item>93 <hi>Ovid</hi>'s Art and Remedy of Love 1662</item>
                  <item>94 <hi>Quevedoes</hi> Viſions compleat, in two Vol. <hi>London</hi> 1678-82</item>
                  <item>95 <hi>Spaniſh</hi> Critick, Tranſlated by <hi>Paul Rycaut</hi> 1681</item>
                  <item>96 Secretary in Faſhion, or an Elegant way of writing Letters 1683</item>
                  <item>97 Ten P<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>eaſures of Marriage (with Figures) 1683</item>
                  <item>98 The Preſent State of <hi>Betty-Land</hi> 1684</item>
                  <item>99 Travels of Father <hi>Chriſtmas</hi> over all the World</item>
                  <item>100 Wits Cabinet, or the Art of Wooing and making Love 1684</item>
                  <item>101 Woman as good as the Man, or equality of both Sexes 1677</item>
                  <item>102 <hi>Withers (Geor.)</hi> Abuſes Stript and Whipt, <hi>Epithalamia, Motto,</hi> &amp;c. 1622</item>
                  <item>103 <hi>York ſhire</hi> 
                     <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ogue, or Life of <hi>William Neviſon,</hi> a Highway-man 1684</item>
                  <item>104 Six Novels <hi>(viz.)</hi> Madam and Count <hi>d'Guiche.</hi> Amours of <hi>Donna Sforz<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                           <desc>•</desc>
                        </gap>,</hi> Queen of <hi>Polonia.</hi> Amorous Conqueſts of the Great <hi>Alexander.</hi> Adamites, or the Intrigues of Father <hi>Rock</hi> with the Nuns. Triumphs of Love and Friendſhip. <hi>Diomedes,</hi> or the <hi>Dutch</hi> Rogue (with Figures.)</item>
                  <item>105 Six Novels <hi>(viz.) Don Sebaſtian,</hi> King of <hi>Portugal. Eve</hi> Reviv'd, or the Fair one ſtark Naked. <hi>Eromena,</hi> or the Noble Stranger. Extravagant Poet. Fugitive States<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man. Female Prince, or <hi>Frederick</hi> of <hi>Scicily.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>106 Six Novels <hi>(viz.) London</hi> Bully, or the Prodigal Son. <hi>London</hi> Jilt, or the Politick Whore, in two Vol. Triumphs of Love and Friendſhip. Obliging Miſtreſs, or the Faſhionable Gallant. <hi>Diomedes,</hi> or the <hi>Dutch</hi> Rogue (with Figures.)</item>
                  <item>107 Six Novels <hi>(viz.)</hi> Perplext Princeſs. Priviledge of Cuckolds, or Cure of Jealouſie. Princeſs of <hi>Montferrat.</hi> Parliament of Women. <hi>Romulus</hi> and <hi>Tarquin.</hi> Travels of <hi>Don Franciſco de Quevedo.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <pb n="27" facs="tcp:46599:18"/>
                  <item>108 Six Novels <hi>(viz.)</hi> Unequalled Match. Triumphs of Love and Friendſhip. Unſatis<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fied Lovers. <hi>Diomedes,</hi> or the <hi>Dutch</hi> Rogue (with Figures.) The Lovely Polander. The Pilgrim.</item>
                  <item>109 Six Novels <hi>(viz.) Neopolitan,</hi> or the Defender of his Miſtreſs. Amours of Madam and Count <hi>d' Guiche.</hi> Amorous Conqueſts of the Great <hi>Alexander. Don Sebaſtian,</hi> King of <hi>Portugal.</hi> Fugitive States-man. <hi>London</hi> Bully, or the Prodigal Son</item>
                  <item>110 Six Novels <hi>(viz.)</hi> Amours of <hi>Bonne Sforza</hi> Queen of <hi>Polonia. Eue</hi> revived, or the Fair One ſtark naked. Lovely <hi>Polander. Beraldus</hi> Prince of <hi>Savoy.</hi> Triumphs of Love and Friendſhip. Priviledges of Cuckolds, or Cure of Jealoſie.</item>
                  <item>111 Six Novels <hi>(viz.)</hi> Princeſs of <hi>Mont-Ferrat.</hi> Travels of <hi>Don Franciſco de Quevedo.</hi> Amorous Conqueſts of the Great <hi>Alexander. Diomedes,</hi> or the <hi>Dutch</hi> Rogue (with Figures.) Priviledge of Cuckolds, or Cure of Jealouſie. Amours of <hi>Donna Sforza</hi> Queen of <hi>Polonia.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>112 Six Novels <hi>(viz.)</hi> Parliament of Women. Amours of <hi>Donna Sforza</hi> Queen of <hi>Polo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nia.</hi> Triumphs of Love and Friendſhip. <hi>Eve</hi> revived or the Fair One ſtark naked. <hi>Diomedes,</hi> or the <hi>Dutch</hi> Rogue (with Figures.</item>
               </list>
            </div>
         </div>
         <div type="list">
            <head>Bundles of Plays. Quarto.</head>
            <list>
               <item>1 SIx Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> The Reformation. The Conſpiracy or Change of Government. Imperial Northern Laſs. Love and Revenge. And Sir <hi>Her<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cules Buffoon</hi>
               </item>
               <item>2 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> The Chances. The Conqueſt of <hi>China.</hi> The Bond-man. The Unfortunate Mother. The Mock Tempeſt, or <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>nchanted Caſtle. And <hi>Piſo</hi>'s Conſpiracy</item>
               <item>3 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> The <hi>Spaniſh</hi> Rogue. The Heir of <hi>Morocco. Sertori<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>us.</hi> The Twins. The Revenge. The Fatal Jealouſie</item>
               <item>4 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz) Paſtor fido,</hi> or the faithful Shepherd. <hi>Ibrahim,</hi> or the Illuſtrious <hi>Baſſa.</hi> Elder Brother. Rival Kings. Counterfeit Bridegroom. And <hi>Alcibiades</hi>
               </item>
               <item>5 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> The <hi>Dutch</hi> Lover. Deſtruction of <hi>Troy. Flora</hi>'s Vagaries. <hi>Herod</hi> and <hi>Mariamne.</hi> The Conſtant Nymph. And the Fatal Love</item>
               <item>6 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> The Amorous Fryars. <hi>Tamerlane</hi> the Great. <hi>Lu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cius Junius Brutus.</hi> Wrangling Lovers. <hi>Othello</hi> the Moor of <hi>Venice.</hi> And the Modiſh Lovers</item>
               <item>7 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(vix.)</hi> The Rivals. The Conſpiracy. The City Madam. <hi>Cambyſes</hi> King of <hi>Perſia.</hi> The Careleſs Lovers. And <hi>Thyeſtes.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>8 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> The Reformation. The Northern Laſs. Imperiale. <hi>Conſtantine</hi> the Great. The Wedding. And the Hiſtory of <hi>Charles</hi> the eighth of <hi>France</hi>
               </item>
               <item>9 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> Wrangling Lovers. <hi>Othell<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi> the Moor of <hi>Venice.</hi> Sir <hi>Fopling Flutter. Venice</hi> preſerved. <hi>Gloriana</hi> and the Plain Dealer.</item>
               <item>10 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> Modiſh Lovers. <hi>Thyeſtes.</hi> The Marchants Wife. The <hi>London</hi> Chaunticleres. Madam <hi>Fickle.</hi> And the Hiſtory of King <hi>Lear</hi>
               </item>
               <item>11 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(vix.)</hi> Dutch Lover. Deſtruction of <hi>Troy.</hi> Miſery of Civil War. Mother <hi>Bombie.</hi> Notes on the Empreſs of <hi>Morocco.</hi> The Libertine</item>
               <item>12 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.) Flora</hi>'s Vagaries. <hi>Herod</hi> and <hi>Mariamne.</hi> The Changeling. Vertue Betrayed, or <hi>Anna Bullen.</hi> The Heir. And the Iſland Princeſs</item>
               <pb n="28" facs="tcp:46599:19"/>
               <item>13 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> The Conſtant Nymph. The Man of <hi>New-Market.</hi> The Old Couple. <hi>Titus</hi> and <hi>Berenice.</hi> The <hi>Hollander.</hi> And the Fatal Love.</item>
               <item>14 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz) Ibrahim</hi> the Illuſtrious <hi>Baſſa.</hi> The Rival Queens. The Twins. Love in a Nunnery. The Loyal General. <hi>Paſtor Fido,</hi> or the Faithful Sheheard</item>
               <item>15 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> The Elder Brother. Love in a Wood. Enchanted Lovers. <hi>Wily</hi> Beguiled. Spightful Siſter. Rival Kings</item>
               <item>16 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> The Defeated Widdow. <hi>Alcibiades,</hi> Loving Enemies. Siege of <hi>Rhodes.</hi> Numerous Lovers. And Injured Princeſs</item>
               <item>17 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> The <hi>Spaniſh</hi> Rogue. The <hi>French</hi> Puritan. <hi>Mithridates</hi> King of <hi>Pontus.</hi> Hiſtory of <hi>Richard</hi> th 2d. Dame <hi>Dobſon.</hi> And the Heir of <hi>Morocco.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>18 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> A Match in New-gate. The Young King. <hi>Titus</hi> and <hi>Berenice,</hi> Sir <hi>Patient Fancy.</hi> The Counterfeits. The Fatal Jealouſie.</item>
               <item>19 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> The Mock Tempeſt. The Atheiſt. The Virtuous Wife. <hi>Macheth.</hi> The Wild Gallant. And <hi>Piſo</hi>'s Conſpiracy</item>
               <item>20 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> The Chances. The Man of Mode. <hi>Chab<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>t</hi> Admiral of <hi>France.</hi> The Generous <hi>Portugal.</hi> The Roman Actor. The Conqueſt of <hi>China.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>21 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> The Poetical Squire. The Humerous Lovers. The Tragedy of <hi>Nero.</hi> The <hi>French</hi> Puritan. The Loving Enemies. And Love and Reveng.</item>
               <item>22 Six Comedies and Tragedies, <hi>&amp;c. (viz.)</hi> The Atheiſt. The Poor Mans Comfort. Fortune by Land and Sea. Wits led by the Noſe. The Fool turn'd Critick. Notes on the Empreſs of <hi>Morocco</hi>
               </item>
               <item>23 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> The Careleſs Lovers. <hi>Tamerlain</hi> the Great. Amo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rous Fryars. Loveſick King. <hi>Lucius Junius Brutus.</hi> The Conſpiracy, or Change of Government.</item>
               <item>24 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz.) Cambyſes</hi> King of <hi>Perſia.</hi> City Madam. <hi>Sertorius.</hi> The Twins. The Wedding. The Rivals.</item>
               <item>25 Six Comedies and Tragedies <hi>(viz) Conſtantine</hi> the Great. The Change of Government. The Love-ſick King. The Bond-man. The Unfortunate Mother. And the Hiſtory of <hi>Charles</hi> the 8th. of <hi>France.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>26 Six Tragi-Comedies <hi>(viz.)</hi> The Poets Revenge. Fortune by Sea and Land. Poor Mans Comfort. Ingratitude of a Common-Wealth. The Treacherous Friend. And the Jealous Bridegroom.</item>
               <item>27 <hi>Alcilia,</hi> with the Love of <hi>Amor</hi> and <hi>Laura. Hero</hi> and <hi>Leander,</hi> by <hi>Marloe. Cynthia</hi>'s Re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>venge. <hi>Aſtrophel</hi> and <hi>Stella.</hi> Wits Pilgrimage. Memorials on Queen <hi>Elizabeth.</hi> The Bride. Young Gallants Whirligigg. <hi>Iter Boriale,</hi> with ſix other curious Poetical Tracts</item>
               <item>28 <hi>Jordan</hi>'s Poetical Varieties. <hi>Opella,</hi> a Poem. <hi>Greſham</hi>'s Choſt. Character of a <hi>London</hi> Diurnal. Parliament of Bees. Feſtival of Light. Knave of Clubs. Complaint of a Popinjay. Battle of Cats. Counter-Scuffle, with ſix other Treatiſes.</item>
               <item>29 Academy of Love. Quips upon Queſtions. Pint of Poetical Sherry. Paſſion of a Diſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>contented Mind. Melancholy Humours, with <hi>Drummonds</hi> Poems, The Vote, or Poem Royal, <hi>Withers. Engliſh</hi> Balm. <hi>Cato</hi>'s Moral Diſticks. Youths Tragedy a Poem, with others</item>
               <item>30 <hi>Paſquil</hi>'s Progreſs to the Tavern. <hi>Hero</hi> and <hi>Leander,</hi> by <hi>Chapman</hi>— Paraphraſe on <hi>So<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lomons</hi> Song. General Defence of Learning, a Poem. <hi>Dick Whippers</hi> Seſſions. Times Whirllgigg. Several Maſques of the Temple, and other Inns-of-Court-Gentlemen. The Watermens Suit againſt Players. Faction of Love and Beauty with others.</item>
            </list>
            <trailer>FINIS.</trailer>
         </div>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>
